<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><updated>2022-04-18T11:48:41+00:00</updated><icon>https://saidit.net/static/icon.png/</icon><id>/s/DownTheMemoryHole/.rss</id><link rel="self" href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/.rss" type="application/atom+xml" /><link rel="alternate" href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/" type="text/html" /><subtitle>Only You can prevent memory holes</subtitle><title>Only you can prevent memory holes</title><entry><author><name>/u/jet199</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/jet199</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/jet199&quot;&gt; /u/jet199 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.ph/2017.11.19-180022/https://www.theguardian.com/society/2004/jul/31/health.socialcare&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/95r5/mistaken_identity_how_the_liberal_media_spoke/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_95r5</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/95r5/mistaken_identity_how_the_liberal_media_spoke/" /><updated>2022-04-17T09:05:34+00:00</updated><title>Mistaken identity - how the liberal media spoke about trans surgery in 2004</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/OnlineBackupArchive</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/OnlineBackupArchive</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/94jz/milton_william_bill_cooper_collection_20th/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/skHgRrV8zg6RKb1yLb3kgesawXQNO2PaOZpVTVCnsjw.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Milton William (Bill) Cooper Collection - 20th Anniversary Edition - [Archive + torrent]&quot; title=&quot;Milton William (Bill) Cooper Collection - 20th Anniversary Edition - [Archive + torrent]&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the complete (unofficial) Bill Cooper Collection.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Contains Mr. Cooper&amp;#39;s &amp;#39;Behold a Pale Horse&amp;#39; - eBook and Audiobook (clear quality) - radio show &amp;#39;Hour Of The Time&amp;#39; (1392 episodes), pictures, presentations, seminars, interviews and documentaries.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Several unlisted HOTT episodes not even available through official channels are featured, also &amp;#39;alternative versions&amp;#39;, recorded by several people while the show was on-air.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Archive includes a comprehensive research library featuring some 4,500+ eBooks (many of which was in Cooper&amp;#39;s actual library), with a focus on liberty, the occult, history, conspiracy, self-governance, self-defense and self-sufficiency.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This collection is aimed at having &amp;#39;everything in one place&amp;#39;, and serves as a &amp;#39;beginner&amp;#39;s pack&amp;#39; as well as provide resources for the ardent researcher and/or archivist.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Other contents include Zapruder (several versions), 6 films, JFK-, WACO- &amp;amp; Moon-files, including documentaries and related documents.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Seeing the theme of Mr. Cooper was one of Freedom, some personal additions have been added due to historical value:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A copy of the United States Constitution (and related writings), Johnny Liberty&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;The Global Sovereign&amp;#39;s Handbook&amp;quot;, as well as the 1560 Geneva Bible (came across the Atlantic on the Mayflower) have thus been included.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;hr/&gt; &lt;p&gt;Main archive is located at:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/details/MiltonWilliamCooper-HourOfTheTime&quot;&gt;https://archive.org/details/MiltonWilliamCooper-HourOfTheTime&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;which includes nodes to all of Mr. Cooper&amp;#39;s content (exclusively).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For main content + &amp;#39;Extra&amp;#39; not available on archive.org (research library, moving pictures and much more) have been compiled into a single torrent, permanently stored under ZIP in the sidebar:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/download/MiltonWilliamCooper-HourOfTheTime/Milton%20William%20Cooper%20Collection%20-%20torrent.zip/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;direct link to torrent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;magnet:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;magnet:?xt=urn:btih:fdea57a069190269a47be459a6ee0cba65904198&amp;amp;dn=Milton%20William%20Cooper&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2ftracker.opentrackr.org%3a1337%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2f9.rarbg.com%3a2810%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2fmovies.zsw.ca%3a6969%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2fbt1.archive.org%3a6969%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2ftracker.opentrackr.org%3a1337&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2fopen.stealth.si%3a80%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2fexodus.desync.com%3a6969%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2fwww.torrent.eu.org%3a451%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2ftracker.torrent.eu.org%3a451%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2ftracker.tiny-vps.com%3a6969%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2ftracker.openbittorrent.com%3a6969%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2ftracker.moeking.me%3a6969%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2ftracker.bitsearch.to%3a1337%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2ftracker.altrosky.nl%3a6969%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2fretracker.lanta-net.ru%3a2710%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2finferno.demonoid.is%3a3391%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2ffe.dealclub.de%3a6969%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2fopentor.org%3a2710%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=udp%3a%2f%2fexplodie.org%3a6969%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=https%3a%2f%2ftracker.nanoha.org%3a443%2fannounce&amp;amp;tr=https%3a%2f%2ftracker.iriseden.fr%3a443%2fannounce &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hash:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;fdea57a069190269a47be459a6ee0cba65904198 &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt; &lt;p&gt;If using Hash, trackers should be added manually, or download could stall:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/download/MiltonWilliamCooper-HourOfTheTime/Milton%20William%20Cooper%20Collection%20-%20torrent.zip/Trackers%20used.txt&quot;&gt;Trackers used&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Size: 97.88 GB&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;hr/&gt; &lt;p&gt;Technical:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enable encryption&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;IPv6 is currently supported, thus multiple streams can be DL at once if you want to.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Preferred Protocol: TCP.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;hr/&gt; &lt;p&gt;For high-quality recordings, and/or just to support the keepers of the official media, I recommend contacting hourofthime.com by ordering these (and other original files) directly from them:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:hourofthetime@hotmail.com&quot;&gt;hourofthetime@hotmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;hr/&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Last updated: 2022-04-17&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you have downloaded a copy before, simply grab the latest torrent, perform a re-check, and continue the download to get the updated files.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Details in the Changelog (linked with the torrent)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/OnlineBackupArchive&quot;&gt; /u/OnlineBackupArchive &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/94jz/milton_william_bill_cooper_collection_20th/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/94jz/milton_william_bill_cooper_collection_20th/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_94jz</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/94jz/milton_william_bill_cooper_collection_20th/" /><updated>2022-04-08T23:09:11+00:00</updated><title>Milton William (Bill) Cooper Collection - 20th Anniversary Edition - [Archive + torrent]</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/wristaction</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/wristaction</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/92xb/carol_shakeshaft_ted_talk_about_school_faculty/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/uDWyHcZllYetT84yx3AJjIf8Sk7WjUxhZQTHNm_t2sk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Carol Shakeshaft TED talk about school faculty child sexual abuse.&quot; title=&quot;Carol Shakeshaft TED talk about school faculty child sexual abuse.&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/wristaction&quot;&gt; /u/wristaction &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W6cl_8_Vxlg&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/92xb/carol_shakeshaft_ted_talk_about_school_faculty/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_92xb</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/92xb/carol_shakeshaft_ted_talk_about_school_faculty/" /><updated>2022-03-29T01:34:27+00:00</updated><title>Carol Shakeshaft TED talk about school faculty child sexual abuse.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nitter.net/wsbgnl/status/1497884096726323201#m&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ywl/previous_and_new_cdc_covid_transmission/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8ywl</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ywl/previous_and_new_cdc_covid_transmission/" /><updated>2022-02-28T04:27:13+00:00</updated><title>Previous and new CDC covid transmission thresholds based on cases per 100,000 population per week. They literally redefined “low” to be higher than the old threshold for “high”. This chart looks like a joke, but it is all too real.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Rastafoo</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Rastafoo</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ya7/former_reddit_ceo_ellen_pao_claims_she_knew_about/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/PCYZRxrba1aPb6grxjjrMA25yWGqurIQky7MDxViG5U.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Former Reddit CEO Ellen Pao Claims She Knew About Epstein-Maxwell Pedo Network, Said Nothing&quot; title=&quot;Former Reddit CEO Ellen Pao Claims She Knew About Epstein-Maxwell Pedo Network, Said Nothing&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Rastafoo&quot;&gt; /u/Rastafoo &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2020/07/06/former-reddit-ceo-ellen-pao-claims-she-knew-about-epstein-maxwell-pedo-network-said-nothing/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ya7/former_reddit_ceo_ellen_pao_claims_she_knew_about/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8ya7</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ya7/former_reddit_ceo_ellen_pao_claims_she_knew_about/" /><updated>2022-02-24T00:06:23+00:00</updated><title>Former Reddit CEO Ellen Pao Claims She Knew About Epstein-Maxwell Pedo Network, Said Nothing</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Rastafoo</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Rastafoo</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican activist Marty Glickman (a.k.a. “Republican Marty”), was taken into custody by Florida police on four counts of unlawful sexual activity with an underage girl and one count of delivering the drug LSD.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican legislative aide Howard L. Brooks was charged with molesting a 12-year old boy and possession of child pornography.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican Senate candidate John Hathaway was accused of having sex with his 12-year old baby sitter and withdrew his candidacy after the allegations were reported in the media.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican preacher Stephen White, who demanded a return to traditional values, was sentenced to jail after offering $20 to a 14-year-old boy for permission to perform oral sex on him.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican talk show host Jon Matthews pleaded guilty to exposing his genitals to an 11 year old girl.Republican anti-gay activist Earl “Butch” Kimmerling was sentenced to 40 years in prison for molesting an 8-year old girl after he attempted to stop a gay couple from adopting her.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican Party leader Paul Ingram pleaded guilty to six counts of raping his daughters and served 14 years in federal prison.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican election board official Kevin Coan was sentenced to two years probation for soliciting sex over the internet from a 14-year old girl.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican politician Andrew Buhr was charged with two counts of first degree sodomy with a 13-year old boy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican politician Keith Westmoreland was arrested on seven felony counts of lewd and lascivious exhibition to girls under the age of 16 (i.e. exposing himself to children).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican anti-abortion activist John Allen Burt was charged with sexual misconduct involving a 15-year old girl.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican County Councilman Keola Childs pleaded guilty to molesting a male child.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican activist John Butler was charged with criminal sexual assault on a teenage girl.Republican candidate Richard Gardner admitted to molesting his two daughters.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican Councilman and former Marine Jack W. Gardner was convicted of molesting a 13-year old girl.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican County Commissioner Merrill Robert Barter pleaded guilty to unlawful sexual contact and assault on a teenage boy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican City Councilman Fred C. Smeltzer, Jr. pleaded no contest to raping a 15 year-old girl and served 6-months in prison.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican activist Parker J. Bena pleaded guilty to possession of child pornography on his home computer and was sentenced to 30 months in federal prison and fined $18,000.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican parole board officer and former Colorado state representative, Larry Jack Schwarz, was fired after child pornography was found in his possession.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican strategist and Citadel Military College graduate Robin Vanderwall was convicted in Virginia on five counts of soliciting sex from boys and girls over the internet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican city councilman Mark Harris, who is described as a “good military man” and “church goer,” was convicted of repeatedly having sex with an 11-year-old girl and sentenced to 12 years in prison.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican businessman Jon Grunseth withdrew his candidacy for Minnesota governor after allegations surfaced that he went swimming in the nude with four underage girls, including his daughter.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican director of the “Young Republican Federation” Nicholas Elizondo molested his 6-year old daughter and was sentenced to six years in prison.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican benefactor of conservative Christian groups, Richard A. Dasen Sr., was charged with rape for allegedly paying a 15-year old girl for sex. Dasen, 62, who is married with grown children and several grandchildren, has allegedly told police that over the past decade he paid more than $1 million to have sex with a large number of young women.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic donor and billionaire, Jeffrey Epstein, ran an underage child sex brothel and was convicted of soliciting underage girls for prostitution.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic New York Congressman, Anthony Weiner, plead guilty to transferring obscene material to a minor as part of a plea agreement for sexted and sending Twitter DMs to underage girls as young as 15.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic donor, activist, and Hollywood producer Harvey Weinstein is being criminally prosecuted and civilly sued for years of sexual abuse (that was well known “secret” in Hollywood) including underage sexual activities with aspiring female actresses.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic activist and #metoo proponent, Asia Argento, settled a lawsuit for sexual harassment stemming from sexual activities with an underage actor.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Mayor of Racine, Wisconsin, Gary Becker, was convicted of attempted child seduction, child pornography, and other child sex crimes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Seattle Mayor Ed Murray resigned after multiple accusations of child sexual abuse were levied against him including by family members.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic activist and aid to NYC Mayor De Blasio, Jacob Schwartz was arrested on possession of 3,000+ child pornographic images.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic activist and actor, Russell Simmons, was sued based on an allegation of sexual assault where he coerced an underage model for sex.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Governor of Oregon, Neil Goldschmidt, after being caught by a newspaper, publicly admitted to having a past sexual relationship with a 13-year-old girl after the statute of limitations on the rape charges had expired.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Illinois Congressman, Mel Reynolds resigned from Congress after he was convicted of statutory rape of a 16-year-old campaign volunteer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic New York Congressman, Fred Richmond, was arrested in Washington D.C. for soliciting sex from a 16-year-old boy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic activist, donor, and director, Roman Polanski, fled the country after pleading guilty to statutory rape of a 13-year-old girl. Democrats and Hollywood actors still defend him to this day, including, Whoopi Goldberg, Martin Scorcese, Woody Allen, David Lynch, Wim Wenders, Pedro Almodovar, Tilda Swinton and Monica Bellucci.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic State Senator from Alaska, George Jacko, was found guilty of sexual harassment of an underage legislative page.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic State Representative candidate for Colorado, Andrew Myers, was convicted for possession of child pornography and enticing children.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Illinois Congressman, Gus Savage was investigated by the Democrat-controlled House Committee on Ethics for attempting to rape an underage female Peace Corps volunteer in Zaire. The Committee concluded that while the events did occur his apology was sufficient and took no further action.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic activist, donor, and spokesperson for Subway, Jared Fogle, was convicted of distribution and receipt of child pornography and traveling to engage in illicit sexual conduct with a minor.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic State Department official, Carl Carey, under Hillary Clinton’s state department, was arrested on ten counts of child porn possession.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Maine Assistant Attorney General, James Cameron, was sentenced to just over 15 years in federal prison for seven counts of child porn possession, receipt and transmission.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic State Department official, Daniel Rosen, under Hillary Clinton’s state department, was arrested and charged with allegedly soliciting sex from a minor over the internet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic State Department official, James Cafferty, pleaded guilty to one count of transportation of child pornography.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic radio host, Bernie Ward, plead guilty to one count of sending child pornography over the Internet.Democratic deputy attorney general from California, Raymond Liddy, was arrested for possession of child pornography.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Illinois State Representative, Keith Farnham, has resigned and was charged with possession of child pornography and has been accused of bragging at an online site about sexually molesting a 6-year-old girl.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic spokesperson for the Arkansas Democratic Party, Harold Moody, Jr, was charged with distribution and possession of child pornography.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Radnor Township Board of Commissioners member, Philip Ahr, resigned from his position after being charged with possession of child pornography and abusing children between 2 and 6 years-old.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic activist and BLM organizer, Charles Wade, was arrested and charged with human trafficking and underage prostitution.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Texas attorney and activist, Mark Benavides, was charged with having sex with a minor, inducing a child under 18 to have sex and compelling prostitution of at least nine legal clients and possession of child pornography. He was found guilty on six counts of sex trafficking.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Virginia Delegate, Joe Morrissey, was indicted on charges connected to his relationship with a 17-year-old girl and was charged with supervisory indecent liberties with a minor, electronic solicitation of a minor, possession of child pornography and distribution of child pornography.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Massachusetts Congressman, Gerry Studds, was censured by the House of Representatives after he admitted to an inappropriate relationship with a 17-year-old page.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Former Mayor of Stillwater, New York, Rick Nelson was plead guilty to five counts of possession of child pornography of children less than 16 years of age.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Former Mayor of Clayton, New York, Dale Kenyon, was indicted for sexual acts against a teenager.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Former Mayor of Hubbard, Ohio, Richard Keenan, was given a life sentence in jail for raping a 4-year-old girl.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Former Mayor of Winston, Oregeon, Kenneth Barrett, was arrested for setting up a meeting to have sex with a 14-year-old girl who turned out to be a police officer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Former Mayor of Randolph, Nebraska, Dwayne L. Schutt, was arrested and charged with four counts of felony third-degree sexual assault of a child and one count of intentional child abuse.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Former Mayor of Dawson, Georgia, Christopher Wright, was indicted on the charges of aggravated child molestation, aggravated sodomy, rape, child molestation and statutory rape of an 11-year-old boy and a 12-year-old girl.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Former Mayor of Stockton, California, Anthony Silva, was charged with providing alcohol to young adults during a game of strip poker that included a 16-year-old boy at a camp for underprivileged children run by the mayor.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Former Mayor of Millbrook, New York, Donald Briggs, was arrested and charged with inappropriate sexual contact with a person younger than 17.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic party leader for Victoria County, Texas, Stephen Jabbour, plead guilty to possession and receiving over half a million child pornographic images.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic activist and fundraiser, Terrence Bean, was arrested on charges of sodomy and sex abuse in a case involving a 15-year-old boy and when the alleged victim declined to testify, and the judge dismissed the case.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Party Chairman for Davidson County, Tennessee, Rodney Mullin, resigned amid child pornography allegations.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic activist, Andrew Douglas Reed, pleaded guilty to a multiple counts of 2nd-degree sexual exploitation of a minor for producing child pornography.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic official from Terre Haute, Indiana, David Roberts was sentenced to federal prison for producing and possessing child pornography including placing hidden cameras in the bedrooms and bathrooms at a home he shared with two minor female victims.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic California Congressman, Tony Cárdenas, is being sued in LA County for allegedly sexually abused a 16-year-old girl.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic aide to Senator Barbara Boxer, Jeff Rosato, plead guilty to charges of trading in child pornography.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic Alaskan State Representative, Dean Westlake, resigned from his seat after the media published a report alleging he fathered a child with a 16-year-old girl when he was 28.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Democratic New Jersey State Assemblyman, Neil Cohen, was convicted of possession and distribution of child pornography.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican Tim Nolan, chairman of Donald Trump’s presidential campaign in Kentucky, pled guilty to child sex trafficking and on February 11, 2018 he was sentenced to serve 20 years in prison.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican state Senator Ralph Shortey was indicted on four counts of human trafficking and child pornography. In November 2017, he pleaded guilty to one count of child sex trafficking in exchange for the dropping of the other charges.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican anti-abortion activist Howard Scott Heldreth is a convicted child rapist in Florida.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican County Commissioner David Swartz pleaded guilty to molesting two girls under the age of 11 and was sentenced to 8 years in prison.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican judge Mark Pazuhanich pleaded no contest to fondling a 10-year old girl and was sentenced to 10 years probation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican anti-abortion activist Nicholas Morency pleaded guilty to possessing child pornography on his computer and offering a bounty to anybody who murders an abortion doctor.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican legislator Edison Misla Aldarondo was sentenced to 10 years in prison for raping his daughter between the ages of 9 and 17.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican Mayor Philip Giordano is serving a 37-year sentence in federal prison for sexually abusing 8- and 10-year old girls.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican campaign consultant Tom Shortridge was sentenced to three years probation for taking nude photographs of a 15-year old girl.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican Senator Strom Thurmond, a notable racist, had sex with a 15-year old black girl which produced a child.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican pastor Mike Hintz, whom George W. Bush commended during the 2004 presidential campaign, surrendered to police after admitting to a sexual affair with a female juvenile.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican legislator Peter Dibble pleaded no contest to having an inappropriate relationship with a 13-year-old girl.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican Congressman Donald “Buz” Lukens was found guilty of having sex with a female minor and sentenced to one month in jail.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican fundraiser Richard A. Delgaudio was found guilty of child porn charges and paying two teenage girls to pose for sexual photos.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican activist Mark A. Grethen convicted on six counts of sex crimes involving children.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican activist Randal David Ankeney pleaded guilty to attempted sexual assault on a child.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican Congressman Dan Crane had sex with a female minor working as a congressional page.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican activist and Christian Coalition leader Beverly Russell admitted to an incestuous relationship with his step daughter.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican congressman and anti-gay activist Robert Bauman was charged with having sex with a 16-year-old boy he picked up at a gay bar.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Republican Committee Chairman Jeffrey Patti was arrested for distributing a video clip of a 5-year-old girl being raped.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Rastafoo&quot;&gt; /u/Rastafoo &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ya4/a_very_long_list_of_us_politicians_donors_and/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ya4/a_very_long_list_of_us_politicians_donors_and/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8ya4</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ya4/a_very_long_list_of_us_politicians_donors_and/" /><updated>2022-02-24T00:03:22+00:00</updated><title>A VERY long list of U.S. politicians, donors and political figures who have been arrested and charged with child rape, abuse, pornography or trafficking in the last few years.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/cottoneyejoe</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/cottoneyejoe</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/cottoneyejoe&quot;&gt; /u/cottoneyejoe &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://buffalochronicle.com/2019/10/12/costumes-roleplay-wet-a-young-trudeaus-sexual-appetite/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8yey/costumes_roleplay_whet_a_young_trudeaus_sexual/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8yey</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8yey/costumes_roleplay_whet_a_young_trudeaus_sexual/" /><updated>2022-02-24T16:11:54+00:00</updated><title>Costumes, roleplay whet a young Trudeau’s sexual appetite</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Rastafoo</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Rastafoo</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Rastafoo&quot;&gt; /u/Rastafoo &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nayadaur.tv/2020/09/over-82-per-cent-of-rapists-are-fathers-or-brothers-of-victim-pti-mna/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ya2/pakistan_over_82_per_cent_of_rapists_are_fathers/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8ya2</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ya2/pakistan_over_82_per_cent_of_rapists_are_fathers/" /><updated>2022-02-24T00:00:17+00:00</updated><title>PAKISTAN - Over 82 Per Cent Of Rapists Are Fathers Or Brothers Of Victim</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/jet199</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/jet199</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/jet199&quot;&gt; /u/jet199 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.docdroid.net/i6OTOGZ/winnicott-some-thoughts-on-the-word-democracy-written-1950-pdf&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8y22/some_thoughts_on_the_meaning_of_the_word/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8y22</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8y22/some_thoughts_on_the_meaning_of_the_word/" /><updated>2022-02-22T12:02:50+00:00</updated><title>Some Thoughts on the Meaning of the Word ‘Democracy' - Donald Winnicott</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/jet199</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/jet199</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/jet199&quot;&gt; /u/jet199 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.is/2022.02.20-065132/https://www.huffpost.com/archive/ca/entry/trudeau-dictator_b_6314494&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8xvn/why_canada_will_become_a_dictatorship_under/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8xvn</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8xvn/why_canada_will_become_a_dictatorship_under/" /><updated>2022-02-20T08:23:52+00:00</updated><title>Why Canada Will Become a Dictatorship Under Trudeau</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8xh7/blm_assassin_joins_waukesha_killer_in_the_memory/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/uHIu0xvDwY6tOWARTCOdez0TDrDIvuX8TAssdYXuuwk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;BLM Assassin Joins Waukesha Killer In The Memory Hole&quot; title=&quot;BLM Assassin Joins Waukesha Killer In The Memory Hole&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/Rv39MbDSS9M&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8xh7/blm_assassin_joins_waukesha_killer_in_the_memory/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8xh7</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8xh7/blm_assassin_joins_waukesha_killer_in_the_memory/" /><updated>2022-02-17T05:14:17+00:00</updated><title>BLM Assassin Joins Waukesha Killer In The Memory Hole</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/IkeConn</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/IkeConn</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/IkeConn&quot;&gt; /u/IkeConn &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pagesix.com/2022/01/27/bridget-fonda-seen-for-first-time-in-12-years-on-58th-birthday/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8uv6/bridget_fonda_seen_for_first_time_in_12_years_on/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8uv6</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8uv6/bridget_fonda_seen_for_first_time_in_12_years_on/" /><updated>2022-01-31T03:46:44+00:00</updated><title>Bridget Fonda seen for first time in 12 years on 58th birthday</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8tkt/mars_the_company_lecturing_to_us_about_their_woke/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/N__tcKb7-GnfZYJLXbY0dIBBBgjbATjapXGK7nxQsOs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mars, the company lecturing to us about their woke M&amp;amp;Ms, uses child slavery to produce their chocolate products and is getting majorly sued because of it. Always, these SJWs project their faults onto us and then accuse us so that they can relieve damaging cognitive dissonance.&quot; title=&quot;Mars, the company lecturing to us about their woke M&amp;amp;Ms, uses child slavery to produce their chocolate products and is getting majorly sued because of it. Always, these SJWs project their faults onto us and then accuse us so that they can relieve damaging cognitive dissonance.&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2021/feb/12/mars-nestle-and-hershey-to-face-landmark-child-slavery-lawsuit-in-us&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8tkt/mars_the_company_lecturing_to_us_about_their_woke/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8tkt</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8tkt/mars_the_company_lecturing_to_us_about_their_woke/" /><updated>2022-01-22T10:58:57+00:00</updated><title>Mars, the company lecturing to us about their woke M&amp;Ms, uses child slavery to produce their chocolate products and is getting majorly sued because of it. Always, these SJWs project their faults onto us and then accuse us so that they can relieve damaging cognitive dissonance.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8szs/fbi_claims_synagogue_attack_had_nothing_to_do/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/ZZaikwsObG7T6RKxOrgJPzf0FW6J10MvZeFp6lG5tlM.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;FBI Claims SYNAGOGUE Attack Had Nothing to Do With the Jewish Community&quot; title=&quot;FBI Claims SYNAGOGUE Attack Had Nothing to Do With the Jewish Community&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/z1fDdZIDrF4&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8szs/fbi_claims_synagogue_attack_had_nothing_to_do/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8szs</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8szs/fbi_claims_synagogue_attack_had_nothing_to_do/" /><updated>2022-01-18T03:02:38+00:00</updated><title>FBI Claims SYNAGOGUE Attack Had Nothing to Do With the Jewish Community</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/runi-the-bear</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/runi-the-bear</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8s9q/sonic_sez/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/NXMnP7x5Z51d6eP8DV-fxIk2SNZ2KbiJ0mB1wNvSIcg.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;sonic sez&quot; title=&quot;sonic sez&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/runi-the-bear&quot;&gt; /u/runi-the-bear &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgflip.com/60qawu.jpg&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8s9q/sonic_sez/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8s9q</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8s9q/sonic_sez/" /><updated>2022-01-11T23:52:20+00:00</updated><title>sonic sez</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/runi-the-bear</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/runi-the-bear</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;i watched a few shorts of it and it was kinda good but also bad. Why? so much animal abuse and it could be caused by themselves or by someone else like flippy for example, he has ptsd and whenever he gets that by seeing stuff that reminds him of war, he flips out and kills someone.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;but the good thing about it is that the characters and the animation style are cute.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;now comes the real answer: kids who are mature to gore or 12+ can watch HTF&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/runi-the-bear&quot;&gt; /u/runi-the-bear &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8s7x/how_old_should_people_be_to_watch_happy_tree/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8s7x/how_old_should_people_be_to_watch_happy_tree/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8s7x</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8s7x/how_old_should_people_be_to_watch_happy_tree/" /><updated>2022-01-11T18:52:51+00:00</updated><title>How old should people be to watch Happy Tree Friends?</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dailywire.com/news/british-newspaper-cancels-person-of-the-year-poll-after-j-k-rowling-runs-away-with-top-spot&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8r0k/britains_guardian_newspaper_conducted_a_poll_of/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8r0k</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8r0k/britains_guardian_newspaper_conducted_a_poll_of/" /><updated>2022-01-01T13:56:00+00:00</updated><title>Britain’s Guardian newspaper conducted a poll of readers to see whom it should nominate as person of the year. J.K. Rowling was winning so badly that they quietly shut down the poll and presumably will not have a person of the year, or if they do, it won’t be the result of a reader’s poll.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8r0w/the_real_conspiracy_theory_marginal_revolution/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/jI8imbeu1oOm4TF61ZyvCDV0-97WnJKP4aNphEdoYkA.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The real conspiracy theory - Marginal REVOLUTION. The public health establishment deliberately delayed the COVID vaccine by a month so it wouldn’t make Trump look good before Election Day.&quot; title=&quot;The real conspiracy theory - Marginal REVOLUTION. The public health establishment deliberately delayed the COVID vaccine by a month so it wouldn’t make Trump look good before Election Day.&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2021/12/the-real-conspiracy-theory.html&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8r0w/the_real_conspiracy_theory_marginal_revolution/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8r0w</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8r0w/the_real_conspiracy_theory_marginal_revolution/" /><updated>2022-01-01T14:23:38+00:00</updated><title>The real conspiracy theory - Marginal REVOLUTION. The public health establishment deliberately delayed the COVID vaccine by a month so it wouldn’t make Trump look good before Election Day.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nypost.com/2021/12/28/randi-weingartens-attempts-to-rewrite-school-closings-history-wont-fly/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8qs8/american_federation_of_teachers_boss_randi/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8qs8</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8qs8/american_federation_of_teachers_boss_randi/" /><updated>2021-12-30T16:31:56+00:00</updated><title>American Federation of Teachers boss Randi Weingarten has learned an important lesson from the pandemic: Parents really resent the fact that she and the union she heads pushed to keep schools closed for so long at the expense of kids. So what’s Weingarten doing? Denying she did any such thing.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8qlr/never_forget_in_2015_bill_clinton_called_donald/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/Z4jF6xpSGzQoTNtpMWKUYM-JXkw3tWdjkX4G8boNL3Q.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Never forget: in 2015 Bill Clinton called Donald Trump and encouraged him to run for president.&quot; title=&quot;Never forget: in 2015 Bill Clinton called Donald Trump and encouraged him to run for president.&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2015/08/bill-clinton-called-donald-trump-before-presidential-run-2016&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8qlr/never_forget_in_2015_bill_clinton_called_donald/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8qlr</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8qlr/never_forget_in_2015_bill_clinton_called_donald/" /><updated>2021-12-29T11:11:56+00:00</updated><title>Never forget: in 2015 Bill Clinton called Donald Trump and encouraged him to run for president.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.takimag.com/article/blue-pills-matter/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8qm6/there_is_no_better_demonstration_of_the_matrixs/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8qm6</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8qm6/there_is_no_better_demonstration_of_the_matrixs/" /><updated>2021-12-29T12:16:06+00:00</updated><title>There is no better demonstration of The Matrix’s concept of the blue pill than that virtually every review of the sequel The Matrix Resurrections refers to the auteurs of the 1999 science-fiction classic and its depressing follow-ups as the “Wachowski sisters.”</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/rolledin</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/rolledin</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seems odd. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/rolledin&quot;&gt; /u/rolledin &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8pyb/why_is_magnora_a_32nd_rank_mason/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8pyb/why_is_magnora_a_32nd_rank_mason/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8pyb</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8pyb/why_is_magnora_a_32nd_rank_mason/" /><updated>2021-12-23T06:59:45+00:00</updated><title>Why is magnora a 32nd rank mason?</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ConceptualJames/status/1470909771066888196&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8p07/espn_today_last_year_a_noose_was_found_in_bubba/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8p07</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8p07/espn_today_last_year_a_noose_was_found_in_bubba/" /><updated>2021-12-15T07:43:06+00:00</updated><title>ESPN today: &quot;Last year, a noose was found in Bubba Wallace's stall&quot;. From ESPN.com June 2020: &quot;Wallace not victim of hate crime&quot;. For those who don't recall, the 'noose' was the pull for the garage door. We know that thanks to the FBI agents who were immediately dispatched to investigate.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofx/lets_remember_how_michelle_obama_and_the_corrupt/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/_8K3XnEvumYXywTTFSTnkWk1YNFUM_aTdr4eXTf-hs8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Let’s remember how Michelle Obama and the corrupt Chicago prosecutor Kim Foxx almost got #Jussie off the hook. Only the public outcry got Jussie prosecuted. These two slimy characters are complicit in the attempt to cover up Jussie’s hate crime, even if they weren’t charged and found guilty for it&quot; title=&quot;Let’s remember how Michelle Obama and the corrupt Chicago prosecutor Kim Foxx almost got #Jussie off the hook. Only the public outcry got Jussie prosecuted. These two slimy characters are complicit in the attempt to cover up Jussie’s hate crime, even if they weren’t charged and found guilty for it&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/hoV6Osf.jpg&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofx/lets_remember_how_michelle_obama_and_the_corrupt/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8ofx</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofx/lets_remember_how_michelle_obama_and_the_corrupt/" /><updated>2021-12-10T13:17:17+00:00</updated><title>Let’s remember how Michelle Obama and the corrupt Chicago prosecutor Kim Foxx almost got #Jussie off the hook. Only the public outcry got Jussie prosecuted. These two slimy characters are complicit in the attempt to cover up Jussie’s hate crime, even if they weren’t charged and found guilty for it</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofw/the_cast_of_the_big_bang_theory_supports_jussie/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/g7nSj_hNOwnTgabzvGy1t5p9-cLdK6qNyZDho6ZpE3E.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The cast of the Big Bang Theory supports Jussie Smollett - who committed a hate crime. Oh well, at least it's less time for them to molest children.&quot; title=&quot;The cast of the Big Bang Theory supports Jussie Smollett - who committed a hate crime. Oh well, at least it's less time for them to molest children.&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/JUA679L.jpg&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofw/the_cast_of_the_big_bang_theory_supports_jussie/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8ofw</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofw/the_cast_of_the_big_bang_theory_supports_jussie/" /><updated>2021-12-10T13:14:56+00:00</updated><title>The cast of the Big Bang Theory supports Jussie Smollett - who committed a hate crime. Oh well, at least it's less time for them to molest children.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofu/just_a_reminder_of_the_hate_jussie_smollett/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/xTptA3OOP2K_N2n6FPgvE8rOTRiMvWtpUIuZ4T41Qn4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Just a reminder of the hate Jussie Smollett inspired with his fake hate crime. Look at all the bluechecks lining up to support him. Sanders, Biden, Harris, they're all here. I wonder what they'd say today if anyone in the media had the guts to confront them?&quot; title=&quot;Just a reminder of the hate Jussie Smollett inspired with his fake hate crime. Look at all the bluechecks lining up to support him. Sanders, Biden, Harris, they're all here. I wonder what they'd say today if anyone in the media had the guts to confront them?&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/j5iyKH2.jpg&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofu/just_a_reminder_of_the_hate_jussie_smollett/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8ofu</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofu/just_a_reminder_of_the_hate_jussie_smollett/" /><updated>2021-12-10T13:09:08+00:00</updated><title>Just a reminder of the hate Jussie Smollett inspired with his fake hate crime. Look at all the bluechecks lining up to support him. Sanders, Biden, Harris, they're all here. I wonder what they'd say today if anyone in the media had the guts to confront them?</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofv/jussie_smollett_on_hate_it_never_ceases_to_amaze/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/N29M-M7mzko8WcbzEud-gO4NSt5lnaICUS-40YriVOM.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jussie Smollett on hate. It never ceases to amaze me how hate filled their rants are as they go on about how hateful conservatives are. Didn't Smollett say how offended he was by the &amp;quot;n word&amp;quot;? Or was that only when other people say it?&quot; title=&quot;Jussie Smollett on hate. It never ceases to amaze me how hate filled their rants are as they go on about how hateful conservatives are. Didn't Smollett say how offended he was by the &amp;quot;n word&amp;quot;? Or was that only when other people say it?&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/jzLKBJv.png&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofv/jussie_smollett_on_hate_it_never_ceases_to_amaze/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8ofv</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ofv/jussie_smollett_on_hate_it_never_ceases_to_amaze/" /><updated>2021-12-10T13:13:22+00:00</updated><title>Jussie Smollett on hate. It never ceases to amaze me how hate filled their rants are as they go on about how hateful conservatives are. Didn't Smollett say how offended he was by the &quot;n word&quot;? Or was that only when other people say it?</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/09/01/ruth-bader-ginsburg-officiates-couples-wedding/3453910001/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8nkb/hey_remember_when_ruth_bader_ginsburg_officiated/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8nkb</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8nkb/hey_remember_when_ruth_bader_ginsburg_officiated/" /><updated>2021-12-03T16:51:39+00:00</updated><title>Hey remember when Ruth Bader Ginsburg officiated a maskless wedding during a global pandemic and then croaked two weeks later? No? Weird.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Rastafoo</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Rastafoo</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Rastafoo&quot;&gt; /u/Rastafoo &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://wolfballs.com/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8nbp/lemmy_hates_wolfballs_the_libertarian_spinoff_of/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8nbp</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8nbp/lemmy_hates_wolfballs_the_libertarian_spinoff_of/" /><updated>2021-12-02T04:34:51+00:00</updated><title>Lemmy Hates WolfBalls - the libertarian spinoff of Lemmy</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8n4i/2010_twitter_ceo_dick_costolo_claims_that_were/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/eCeurlf1IY9x1uYvjBXDfh5w20jiDuAdOjVMg_GHRH0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2010: Twitter CEO Dick Costolo claims that “We’re the free speech wing of the free speech party.”&quot; title=&quot;2010: Twitter CEO Dick Costolo claims that “We’re the free speech wing of the free speech party.”&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/sections/alltechconsidered/2013/03/21/174858681/on-its-7th-birthday-is-twitter-still-the-free-speech-party&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8n4i/2010_twitter_ceo_dick_costolo_claims_that_were/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8n4i</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8n4i/2010_twitter_ceo_dick_costolo_claims_that_were/" /><updated>2021-11-30T17:38:45+00:00</updated><title>2010: Twitter CEO Dick Costolo claims that “We’re the free speech wing of the free speech party.”</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8n46/waukesha_has_already_been_stuffed_down_the_memory/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/wbbhzq4-je7iVSbs70oD5p7hVsNVnPe02ZKFbUaBqyc.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Waukesha Has Already Been Stuffed Down The Memory Hole&quot; title=&quot;Waukesha Has Already Been Stuffed Down The Memory Hole&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/X-lYzk0-mUo&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8n46/waukesha_has_already_been_stuffed_down_the_memory/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8n46</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8n46/waukesha_has_already_been_stuffed_down_the_memory/" /><updated>2021-11-30T17:10:46+00:00</updated><title>Waukesha Has Already Been Stuffed Down The Memory Hole</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8mss/his_parents_used_his_real_name/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/aEywOLkC0YJuedQzmSSHvrPS7NPWXVAd3ijUp8oDtZ0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;His parents used his real name.&quot; title=&quot;His parents used his real name.&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/tqPxTrx.jpg&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8mss/his_parents_used_his_real_name/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8mss</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8mss/his_parents_used_his_real_name/" /><updated>2021-11-28T18:46:54+00:00</updated><title>His parents used his real name.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8m7f/you_know_things_are_bad_when_even_ghoulish/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/sOn8lrZv4uWOP516eofZAvXYCimboVrke9vcKd0Ien4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;You know things are bad when even ghoulish, war-mongering neocons are calling out the memory holing of the BLM Waukesha Massacre of the Dancing Grannies.&quot; title=&quot;You know things are bad when even ghoulish, war-mongering neocons are calling out the memory holing of the BLM Waukesha Massacre of the Dancing Grannies.&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://media.consumeproduct.win/post/pNL3kojO.jpeg&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8m7f/you_know_things_are_bad_when_even_ghoulish/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8m7f</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8m7f/you_know_things_are_bad_when_even_ghoulish/" /><updated>2021-11-24T10:19:21+00:00</updated><title>You know things are bad when even ghoulish, war-mongering neocons are calling out the memory holing of the BLM Waukesha Massacre of the Dancing Grannies.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8kse/2020_new_york_gov_cuomo_says_trump_has_no/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/IiazY6XZc7BWFofDJCi5mNoeCX0cpr7yBpv2BIPfWOc.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;2020: New York Gov. Cuomo says Trump has no authority to impose quarantine: 'It would be illegal'&quot; title=&quot;2020: New York Gov. Cuomo says Trump has no authority to impose quarantine: 'It would be illegal'&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/28/ny-gov-cuomo-says-trump-has-no-authority-to-impose-quarantine.html&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8kse/2020_new_york_gov_cuomo_says_trump_has_no/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8kse</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8kse/2020_new_york_gov_cuomo_says_trump_has_no/" /><updated>2021-11-14T18:30:06+00:00</updated><title>2020: New York Gov. Cuomo says Trump has no authority to impose quarantine: 'It would be illegal'</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/melanie-arter/trump-nbc-called-me-racist-banning-travel-china&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ksf/2020_nbc_calls_trump_racist_for_banning_travel/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_8ksf</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8ksf/2020_nbc_calls_trump_racist_for_banning_travel/" /><updated>2021-11-14T18:35:21+00:00</updated><title>2020: NBC calls Trump racist for banning travel from China</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8jtc/the_original_coat_of_arms_for_the_fabian_society/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/uj2MEC6DkY8fWEurV34LKLWe69fw1HlWg5SF1rXEtk8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The original coat of arms for the Fabian Society. They really were (and are presently) very blatant about who they are.&quot; title=&quot;The original coat of arms for the Fabian Society. They really were (and are presently) very blatant about who they are.&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://media.communities.win/post/1LbhCmd9.png&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8jtc/the_original_coat_of_arms_for_the_fabian_society/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8jtc</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8jtc/the_original_coat_of_arms_for_the_fabian_society/" /><updated>2021-11-07T05:34:40+00:00</updated><title>The original coat of arms for the Fabian Society. They really were (and are presently) very blatant about who they are.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Chipit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Chipit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8jt1/bill_gates_promised_to_give_away_his_wealth_well/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/Lxh25VRii8bJnIp7ZGmUMhq3w32d6MvkUNEzypAcsfE.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bill Gates Promised to Give Away His Wealth. Well, That Was BS. His net worth has more than doubled in that time.&quot; title=&quot;Bill Gates Promised to Give Away His Wealth. Well, That Was BS. His net worth has more than doubled in that time.&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Chipit&quot;&gt; /u/Chipit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.inc.com/geoffrey-james/bill-gates-promised-to-give-away-his-wealth-well-that-was-bs.html&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8jt1/bill_gates_promised_to_give_away_his_wealth_well/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_8jt1</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/8jt1/bill_gates_promised_to_give_away_his_wealth_well/" /><updated>2021-11-07T04:40:27+00:00</updated><title>Bill Gates Promised to Give Away His Wealth. Well, That Was BS. His net worth has more than doubled in that time.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Questionable</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Questionable</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7w7n/after_years_harassing_the_president_of_the_united/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/9IMqnJu73e5RKJAszoi7Ffs9frDvmcN5xuxwI282wew.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;After Years Harassing the President of the United States, Donald Trump, the Fake-News NY Times Finally Admits, the Steele Dossier Was a Lie that &amp;quot;Never Materialized or Has Been Proved False&amp;quot;&quot; title=&quot;After Years Harassing the President of the United States, Donald Trump, the Fake-News NY Times Finally Admits, the Steele Dossier Was a Lie that &amp;quot;Never Materialized or Has Been Proved False&amp;quot;&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Questionable&quot;&gt; /u/Questionable &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2021/05/years-harassing-president-united-states-donald-trump-ny-times-finally-admits-lie-behind-corrupt-mueller-investigation-including-peepee-lie-never-materializ/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7w7n/after_years_harassing_the_president_of_the_united/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_7w7n</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7w7n/after_years_harassing_the_president_of_the_united/" /><updated>2021-05-24T06:04:23+00:00</updated><title>After Years Harassing the President of the United States, Donald Trump, the Fake-News NY Times Finally Admits, the Steele Dossier Was a Lie that &quot;Never Materialized or Has Been Proved False&quot;</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Questionable</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Questionable</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7vmj/even_though_it_sounds_like_a_paranoid_fever_dream/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/QTbSLsIJSZ4fzvs17nlKffmIa7n09ve_4jcG-ft8QiE.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&amp;quot;Even though it sounds like a paranoid fever dream a well funded cabal of powerful people, ranging across industries and ideologies, working together behind the scenes to influence perceptions, change rules and laws, steer media coverage and control the flow of information.&amp;quot; -time.com&quot; title=&quot;&amp;quot;Even though it sounds like a paranoid fever dream a well funded cabal of powerful people, ranging across industries and ideologies, working together behind the scenes to influence perceptions, change rules and laws, steer media coverage and control the flow of information.&amp;quot; -time.com&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Questionable&quot;&gt; /u/Questionable &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://time.com/5936036/secret-2020-election-campaign/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7vmj/even_though_it_sounds_like_a_paranoid_fever_dream/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_7vmj</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7vmj/even_though_it_sounds_like_a_paranoid_fever_dream/" /><updated>2021-05-15T22:22:46+00:00</updated><title>&quot;Even though it sounds like a paranoid fever dream a well funded cabal of powerful people, ranging across industries and ideologies, working together behind the scenes to influence perceptions, change rules and laws, steer media coverage and control the flow of information.&quot; -time.com</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/RuckusChan</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/RuckusChan</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7sp2/old_adverts_fully_detached_home_finch_and_leslie/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/ZXZtPyikL3IRa84CTPHUdOphmrMRVxIHlRnblrpH2CA.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Old Adverts - Fully detached home, Finch and Leslie, Toronto&quot; title=&quot;Old Adverts - Fully detached home, Finch and Leslie, Toronto&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/RuckusChan&quot;&gt; /u/RuckusChan &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://files.catbox.moe/g97h6v.jpeg&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7sp2/old_adverts_fully_detached_home_finch_and_leslie/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_7sp2</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7sp2/old_adverts_fully_detached_home_finch_and_leslie/" /><updated>2021-04-28T20:13:22+00:00</updated><title>Old Adverts - Fully detached home, Finch and Leslie, Toronto</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Questionable</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Questionable</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7ssm/in_2007_the_fda_inspected_a_vaccine_manufacturing/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/mqTCaA1BHbcEMcERRAIbHu1_hKLQh-xhqC7cZSwSfJg.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;In 2007 the FDA inspected a vaccine manufacturing plant, things didn’t go well, here is a record of the resulting warning letter which has now been memory-holed&quot; title=&quot;In 2007 the FDA inspected a vaccine manufacturing plant, things didn’t go well, here is a record of the resulting warning letter which has now been memory-holed&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Questionable&quot;&gt; /u/Questionable &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://web.archive.org/web/20080502043538/https://www.fda.gov/foi/warning_letters/s6756c.htm&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7ssm/in_2007_the_fda_inspected_a_vaccine_manufacturing/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_7ssm</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7ssm/in_2007_the_fda_inspected_a_vaccine_manufacturing/" /><updated>2021-04-29T07:27:55+00:00</updated><title>In 2007 the FDA inspected a vaccine manufacturing plant, things didn’t go well, here is a record of the resulting warning letter which has now been memory-holed</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Questionable</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Questionable</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7s6w/let_my_wife_come_home_joe_biden_has_super_awkward/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/IQJfylPv5M8_7cSpdQgITGFhTxJI11OsJlpyLH922VM.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&amp;quot;Let My Wife Come Home!&amp;quot; - Joe Biden Has Super Awkward Exchange with Navajo Nation During Climate Summit (VIDEO)&quot; title=&quot;&amp;quot;Let My Wife Come Home!&amp;quot; - Joe Biden Has Super Awkward Exchange with Navajo Nation During Climate Summit (VIDEO)&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Questionable&quot;&gt; /u/Questionable &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2021/04/let-wife-come-home-joe-biden-super-awkward-exchange-navajo-nation-climate-summit-video/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7s6w/let_my_wife_come_home_joe_biden_has_super_awkward/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_7s6w</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7s6w/let_my_wife_come_home_joe_biden_has_super_awkward/" /><updated>2021-04-26T03:34:45+00:00</updated><title>&quot;Let My Wife Come Home!&quot; - Joe Biden Has Super Awkward Exchange with Navajo Nation During Climate Summit (VIDEO)</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/RelianceTrust</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/RelianceTrust</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7hn3/who_is_the_cdc_and_when_did_you_become_their_bitch/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/Awz7zf8cehO2foMpcoBujJEbd-0A8E9wt5lgv5OdXxQ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Who is the CDC and when did you become their bitch?&quot; title=&quot;Who is the CDC and when did you become their bitch?&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/RelianceTrust&quot;&gt; /u/RelianceTrust &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/8Bqy3vwhHZ8&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7hn3/who_is_the_cdc_and_when_did_you_become_their_bitch/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_7hn3</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7hn3/who_is_the_cdc_and_when_did_you_become_their_bitch/" /><updated>2021-03-03T17:30:39+00:00</updated><title>Who is the CDC and when did you become their bitch?</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/JasonCarswell</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/JasonCarswell</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7h7k/tyler_cook_aka_memoryhold_truthseeker/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/eEGVUEkDHFdJ4eEbgkOE2DHrQwAHQBPqTZzFynlAOig.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tyler Cook, aka MemoryHold, truth-seeker&quot; title=&quot;Tyler Cook, aka MemoryHold, truth-seeker&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tyler Cook, aka MemoryHold, truth-seeker&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;MemoryHold&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://BitChute.com/channel/2VDYfVPMsxHu/&quot;&gt;https://BitChute.com/channel/2VDYfVPMsxHu/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Memory Hold 2.0:&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://YouTube.com/channel/UCZO9sqD9NnRdz3djFQURrvw/videos&quot;&gt;https://YouTube.com/channel/UCZO9sqD9NnRdz3djFQURrvw/videos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;MemoryHold&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://DLive.tv/MemoryHold&quot;&gt;https://DLive.tv/MemoryHold&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALL LINKS:&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://LinkTr.ee/MemoryHold&quot;&gt;https://LinkTr.ee/MemoryHold&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Twitter: @MemoryHold&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MemoryHold&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/MemoryHold&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;Account suspended&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;Twitter suspends accounts which violate the Twitter Rules&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Parler: @MemoryHold&lt;br/&gt; Gab: @MemoryHold&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://Patreon.com/Memoryhold&quot;&gt;https://Patreon.com/Memoryhold&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tyler Cook&lt;br/&gt; @MemoryHold7707&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.paypal.com/paypalme/MemoryHold7707?loca=&quot;&gt;https://www.paypal.com/paypalme/MemoryHold7707?loca=&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tips and Business Inquiries:&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:MemoryHold7@protonmail.com&quot;&gt;MemoryHold7@protonmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Instagram: MemoryHold7 &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;MemoryHold&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://Instagram.com/memoryhold7/?hl=en&quot;&gt;https://Instagram.com/memoryhold7/?hl=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;Sorry, this page isn&amp;#39;t available.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &amp;nbsp; &lt;em&gt;The link you followed may be broken, or the page may have been removed. Go back to Instagram.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Among other episodes and appearances, discovered via:&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;/s/TheUnionOfTheUnwanted/comments/7gr5/union_of_the_unwanted_20_21210_the_union_of_the/&quot;&gt;/s/TheUnionOfTheUnwanted/comments/7gr5/union_of_the_unwanted_20_21210_the_union_of_the/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/JasonCarswell&quot;&gt; /u/JasonCarswell &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7h7k/tyler_cook_aka_memoryhold_truthseeker/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7h7k/tyler_cook_aka_memoryhold_truthseeker/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_7h7k</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7h7k/tyler_cook_aka_memoryhold_truthseeker/" /><updated>2021-03-01T21:52:58+00:00</updated><title>Tyler Cook, aka MemoryHold, truth-seeker</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/wristaction</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/wristaction</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is a kinda memory-holish thing I keep coming back to, or at least something suggestive of propaganda priming afoot which no one seems to refer to. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Long before January 2020, I want to say at least as far back as 2018, the rage among the &lt;em&gt;bien pensants&lt;/em&gt; of reddit was the existence of antivaxxers. It was intense, wide-ranging and sustained. &amp;quot;Antivaxxer&amp;quot; was thrown around like &amp;quot;racist&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;homophobe&amp;quot; and anti-antivaxxer histrionics polluted every sub and, at one point, most threads. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It always seemed forced to me. Not that it wasn&amp;#39;t pursued with extreme zeal, but that the zeal was fixed around a strategic instrument, like a campaign of one sort or another. At the time I suspected that this &lt;em&gt;anti-antivaxxer as a political identity&lt;/em&gt; phenomenon was Democrats in pursuit of their Bush-era &amp;#39;&lt;em&gt;antiscience Christian&lt;/em&gt;&amp;#39; kulturkamph, attempting to re-tool it for an era in which kicking at Christians is clearly kicking down at a defeated opponent. I&amp;#39;m sure for many it was. It could also have been a flex from Big Pharma. Years before, Big Pharma rolled out it&amp;#39;s genital warts vaccine, seeking a nationwide windfall of public school money, with an astroturf campaign which warned parents not to be like those &lt;em&gt;Christians&lt;/em&gt; who&amp;#39;d rather their daughters &lt;em&gt;die of cervical cancer than protect them from an STD&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In any case, it&amp;#39;d be interesting to see when and how the great anti-antivaxxer scare of 201n got started and when it petered out. I use the custom time span filter on google and it kicks back stuff from two months ago. If anyone has any informed guesses or familiarity with the phenomenon, please discuss. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/wristaction&quot;&gt; /u/wristaction &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7go5/reddits_precovid_antiantivaxxer_hysteria_trying/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7go5/reddits_precovid_antiantivaxxer_hysteria_trying/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_7go5</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7go5/reddits_precovid_antiantivaxxer_hysteria_trying/" /><updated>2021-02-26T23:19:33+00:00</updated><title>Reddit's pre-covid anti-antivaxxer hysteria: Trying to nail down the time frame.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/rubberbiscuit</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/rubberbiscuit</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7c8q/disneyland_in_1969_and_in_2019_what_a_difference/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/goI_N0Ll20v3CnB3y53RPNWq_D7rGfxyT_xPkvQeKnU.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Disneyland in 1969 and in 2019 (What a difference 50 years can make). This video is more about race; my reason for sharing is more about weight. Look how fat everyone is compared with 1969&quot; title=&quot;Disneyland in 1969 and in 2019 (What a difference 50 years can make). This video is more about race; my reason for sharing is more about weight. Look how fat everyone is compared with 1969&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/rubberbiscuit&quot;&gt; /u/rubberbiscuit &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitchute.com/video/ePfiGo2ufYt3/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7c8q/disneyland_in_1969_and_in_2019_what_a_difference/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_7c8q</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7c8q/disneyland_in_1969_and_in_2019_what_a_difference/" /><updated>2021-02-07T21:02:08+00:00</updated><title>Disneyland in 1969 and in 2019 (What a difference 50 years can make). This video is more about race; my reason for sharing is more about weight. Look how fat everyone is compared with 1969</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/RelianceTrust</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/RelianceTrust</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7ag7/something_every_gardener_or_permaculture/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/goKSjkx9gp6ny3GoUY8E6H_hqJQp68dEIeX5I8mrlJ0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Something Every Gardener or Permaculture Enthusiast should know - The Amazing ways Harvard Controls&quot; title=&quot;Something Every Gardener or Permaculture Enthusiast should know - The Amazing ways Harvard Controls&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/RelianceTrust&quot;&gt; /u/RelianceTrust &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/aejAstH8hys&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7ag7/something_every_gardener_or_permaculture/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_7ag7</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/7ag7/something_every_gardener_or_permaculture/" /><updated>2021-01-31T16:03:37+00:00</updated><title>Something Every Gardener or Permaculture Enthusiast should know - The Amazing ways Harvard Controls</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Artistic-Mastodon-25</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Artistic-Mastodon-25</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dont ever forget that nobody wanted Biden or Harris. Biden&amp;#39;s campaign was dead until he &amp;quot;won&amp;quot; Iowa, South Carolina, Alabama, and Arkansas-- 4 states that Trump won in the presidential election. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now our country is stuck with two people that nobody wanted as president and vice president. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Well played, DNC. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Artistic-Mastodon-25&quot;&gt; /u/Artistic-Mastodon-25 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/71c6/i_dont_know_a_single_person_who_voted_for_biden/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/71c6/i_dont_know_a_single_person_who_voted_for_biden/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_71c6</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/71c6/i_dont_know_a_single_person_who_voted_for_biden/" /><updated>2020-12-22T00:18:41+00:00</updated><title>I dont know a single person who &quot;voted&quot; for Biden or Harris in the DNC primaries. Now we have a Biden/ Harris presidency.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/guidi</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/guidi</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6yzs/contentbestonline/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/QqqV3PTguOZMofvWEY40I53klgNv38vYTPu9er2vujA.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;contentbestonline&quot; title=&quot;contentbestonline&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;in china , we often have a birthday party at home or in a eating place to have the meal collectively. and we usually consume the birthday cake after the meal.occasionally we play a few games during the birthday celebration .for instance,we dance or sing and so on.or we regularly buy a unique present as a birthday gift . we can also make a stunning birthday card as a birthday present .i assume that is also a terrific way due to the fact it&amp;#39;s miles full of pleasant &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.contentbestonline.com&quot;&gt;https://www.contentbestonline.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/guidi&quot;&gt; /u/guidi &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6yzs/contentbestonline/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6yzs/contentbestonline/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_6yzs</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6yzs/contentbestonline/" /><updated>2020-12-10T08:23:47+00:00</updated><title>contentbestonline</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Questionable</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Questionable</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Questionable&quot;&gt; /u/Questionable &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://patents.google.com/patent/US5676977A/en&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6joo/us5676977a_method_of_curing_aids_with_tetrasilver/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_6joo</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6joo/us5676977a_method_of_curing_aids_with_tetrasilver/" /><updated>2020-10-02T21:32:01+00:00</updated><title>US5676977A - Method of curing AIDS with tetrasilver tetroxide molecular crystal devices</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/ANIKAHirsch</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/ANIKAHirsch</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6ctc/from_gender_identity_disorder_to_gender/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/gyPBCntkPrioQfAGg9BuVUgtkPtAf4NvLlnfkkUuUSE.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;From Gender Identity Disorder to Gender Incongruence -- the Normalization of Delusion: OC&quot; title=&quot;From Gender Identity Disorder to Gender Incongruence -- the Normalization of Delusion: OC&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The war is over.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.huffpost.com/entry/the-war-against-trans-chi_b_10636030&quot;&gt;https://www.huffpost.com/entry/the-war-against-trans-chi_b_10636030&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This was the bold declaration of the author of this 2017 article from Huffpost (considered a respectable publication by some).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What war? Did you know we were fighting?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In fact, the author calls it a “War Against Trans Children”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to her, an invisible machine wages a millennia old war against children who refuse to conform. And now it’s over. Won. The children stand victorious. If true, it could be a beautiful story; but let’s investigate what made her finally to declare victory.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As she states,&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The debate about trans care for adults and adolescents is over, and the consensus is global. … the World Health Organization (WHO) will de-psychopathologize adolescent and adult trans persons”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;De-psychopathologize is a word that is not in any dictionary. However, Wikitionary provides this definition for “psychopathologize”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“psychopathologize (third-person singular simple present psychopathologizes, present participle psychopathologizing, simple past and past participle psychopathologized) &amp;quot;(transitive) To bring into the realm of psychopathology; to treat as a mental disorder.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/psychopathologize&quot;&gt;https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/psychopathologize&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now, the WHO pretends to be an organization of medical professionals. Isn’t it the job of medical professionals to “treat as a mental disorder” things which are, in reality, mental disorder? Aha, so the issue at hand is revealed. This entire battle has hinged on a definition change — a change which was made in the publication of the fifth edition of the North American Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders (DSM), and which the WHO has followed suit in editing in its own guidelines. According to the author, they will (and now have)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“remove Gender Identity Disorder in Adolescence and Adulthood from the mental illness classification, and rename it the value-neutral ‘Gender Incongruence’ coding in a new chapter in Sexual Health.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So, let’s take a look at these terms, and then we will determine the reasons this change was a necessary victory for a radical movement.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to the International Encyclopedia of the Social &amp;amp; Behavioral Sciences (2001): &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The gender identity disorders (GID) are defined as disorders in which an individual exhibits marked and persistent identification with the opposite sex and persistent discomfort (dysphoria) with his or her own sex or sense of inappropriateness in the gender role of that sex.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/neuroscience/gender-identity-disorder&quot;&gt;https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/neuroscience/gender-identity-disorder&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The important word in this definition is “disorder”. A disorder means something is not right; something is out of place. It implies a normal, and it implies a deviation. In fact, this disorder carries many unpleasant side effects. As Linda C. Shafer M.D., wrote in Massachusetts General Hospital Handbook of General Hospital Psychiatry (Sixth Edition), (2010):&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“In adolescents and adults, the disturbance is manifested by a variety of symptoms, such as preoccupation with getting rid of primary and secondary sex characteristics (e.g., requests for hormones or surgery), or a belief in being born the wrong sex. By late adolescence or adulthood, 75% of boys with a history of gender identity disorder as a child will have a homosexual or bisexual orientation. Children with gender identity disorder may have co-existing separation anxiety, generalized anxiety, and depression, whereas adolescents are at risk for depression, suicidal ideation, and suicide attempts. Adults with the condition often have co-existing anxiety and depression. Adult males may have a history of transvestic fetishism as well as other paraphilias. Associated personality disorders are common in male patients.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Those without diagnosed Gender Identity Disorder don’t suffer these symptoms at the same rates as those with, and they are not at the same risk for these issues. So, the disorder was defined and understood. That is, until the name and definition were changed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And it was not immediately changed to Gender Incongruence, as the author of the Huffpost article insinuates. In fact, this change had been made years before this article was even published:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“People with gender dysphoria are typically transgender. The diagnostic label gender identity disorder (GID) was used until 2013 with the release of the DSM-5. The condition was renamed to remove the stigma associated with the term disorder.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gender_dysphoria&quot;&gt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gender_dysphoria&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The American Psychiatric Association articulates the philosophy behind the first definition change on their website:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The presence of gender variance is not the pathology but dysphoria is from the distress caused by the body and mind not aligning and/or societal marginalization of gender-variant people. It needs to be ego-dystonic to qualify as a diagnosis and having a discussion with our patients about the diagnosis prior to charting it is necessary and good care.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The DSM–5 articulates explicitly that ‘gender non-conformity is not in itself a mental disorder.’ The 5th edition also includes a separate ‘gender dysphoria in children’ diagnosis and for the first time allows the diagnosis to be given to individuals with disorders of sex development (DSD). DSM–5 also includes the optional ‘post-transition’ specifier to indicate when a particular individual’s gender transition is complete. In this ‘post-transition’ case, the diagnosis of gender dysphoria would no longer apply but the individual may still need ongoing medical care (e.g., hormonal treatment). Nevertheless, discussions continue among advocates and medical professionals about how best to preserve access to gender transition-related health care while also minimizing the degree to which such diagnostic categories stigmatize the very people that physicians are attempting to help.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychiatry.org/psychiatrists/cultural-competency/education/transgender-and-gender-nonconforming-patients/gender-dysphoria-diagnosis&quot;&gt;https://www.psychiatry.org/psychiatrists/cultural-competency/education/transgender-and-gender-nonconforming-patients/gender-dysphoria-diagnosis&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;These distinctions are dense but not subtle. While identification with the opposite sex would be a clear indication of Gender Identity Disorder, that same identification will not be called “Gender Dysphoria” unless the individual experiences distress as a result. Gender Dysphoria is not called a disorder. Its theory does not assume that the identity is out of place. Instead, the identity is affirmed, and only the symptoms are treated. All of this; to suggest that a man who believes he is a woman is not suffering a case of mistaken identity; but, in fact, is exhibiting the appropriate response to existing as a sexed individual. According to the APA: his feelings are not wrong, his body is. Once this frame is established, remedial steps become apparent. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This definition brings with it its own plan of treatment: medical, hormonal, and surgical transition to the opposite sex. And when this “transition” is complete, the individual no longer has Gender Dysphoria. Diagnostically, he cannot, because his identified sex and perceived sex now align. Never-mind that these “post-transition” patients continue to experience higher rates of all the awful symptoms associated with Gender Identity Disorder. That fact is overlooked by the medical professionals who write these guidelines. His distress cannot be attributed to a gender identity mis-match, therefore it cannot be called Gender Dysphoria. In fact, his distress does not fit any umbrella definition in the DSM 5.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That, post-transition, individuals experienced “higher risks for mortality, suicidal behaviour, and psychiatric morbidity” were the results of a 30-year study conducted in Sweden, completed in 2003.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article/file?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0016885&amp;amp;type=printable&quot;&gt;https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article/file?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0016885&amp;amp;type=printable&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And this recent study had similar results:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“They found transgender adolescents (TGAs) had higher rates of suicidal ideation, plans, attempts and attempts requiring medical care compared to [not transgender] teens. They also had higher rates of non-suicidal self-injury, according to ‘Suicidality Disparities between Transgender and Cisgender Adolescents,’ (Thoma BC, et al. Pediatrics. Oct. 14, 2019, &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1542/peds.2019-1183).&quot;&gt;https://doi.org/10.1542/peds.2019-1183).&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.aappublications.org/news/2019/10/14/suicide101419&quot;&gt;https://www.aappublications.org/news/2019/10/14/suicide101419&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And, in a supreme act of demented irony, the suicidality rates for this group, previously considered a symptom of the disorder, are the last line of defense in a line of reasoning which justifies unheard-of treatment.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The Centre for Suicide Prevention recommends medical transition as a method of suicide prevention, on their website:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The decision to medically transition to the gender with which one identifies can be stressful and may place someone more at risk for suicide. However, studies show that once a transition is completed, it does have beneficial effects.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.suicideinfo.ca/resource/transgender-people-suicide/&quot;&gt;https://www.suicideinfo.ca/resource/transgender-people-suicide/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;However, it seems that very little research has been done on this 7-year named disorder. Indeed, even less has been done to study the effects of the recommended treatment for it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It may be a good analogy to suggest that we will one day look back at the current medical treatment schedule for GI individuals as nothing less than a medical lobotomy. It is indeed castration. Naturally, there is some evidence that preventing natural puberty in children leads to cognitive delays in adulthood. (This quote is long but it is very informative.):&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“By 2004, it was known that surgical castration of male animals can lead to ‘profound loss of synaptic density in the hippocampus and changes in learning and memory’[38][39] due to absence of testosterone. Synapses are the junctions between cells through which information is shared by tiny electrical impulses or chemical transmitters. Their reduction implies reduced or altered activity of that region of the brain. GnRH blockers are a means of chemical as opposed to surgical castration, therefore, the effect of reduction of testosterone by blocking the pituitary needed to be elucidated.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“By 2007, as animal and behavioural studies suggested blockers ‘may have significant effects on memory’ their effects were examined in humans. Interference in memory and executive function[40], and abnormal cerebral function was found in women receiving blockers for gynaecological reasons.[41]&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“In 2008, review of the effect of testosterone deprivation due to blockers in men receiving them for prostate cancer raised the ‘strong argument’ that blockers, alone, caused ‘subtle but significant cognitive declines’.[42] Other studies confirmed ‘higher rates … of cognitive impairment’ compared to controls[43], but were denied by some.[44] Laboratory studies were needed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“In 2009, scientists in universities in Glasgow and Oslo had begun collaborative research on the effect of blockers on the behaviour and brains of sheep. These foundational studies revealed that exposure of the pre-pubertal lamb to blockers led to an observable increase in the size of the amygdala[45], that the activities of a large number of genes in the amygdala and hippocampus were altered by the blockers[46] [47] and, not surprisingly, that some aspects of brain function were disturbed [48][49]. Female sheep had less emotional control and were more anxious. Males were more prone to ‘risk taking’ and alterations in emotional reactivity. Males suffered reduction in spatial memory that persisted after treatment.[50]&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“These results suggest that blockers may alter the shape of the brain and the capacity of cells to communicate with each other at a molecular level[51] [52]. This could be due to a direct effect of the loss of GnRH or, alternatively, a reduction in GnRH-dependent production of local neurosteroids involved in the formation of synaptic connections when the brain is developing.[53] [54]&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Contrary to the laboratory studies, a recent study by the Dutch group[55] on its own human patients asserted that no difference could be found in executive function between mid-teens on blockers and controls. Little reassurance can be gained from this conclusion, however, because close reading of the results reveals that males on blockers transgendering to females did have ‘significantly lower accuracy scores than the control groups’. However, the authors declared that ‘it is possible that this is just a chance finding due to the small size of the subgroup (of eight adolescents)’. Alternatively, it could have confirmed what had been revealed in sheep; but, indeed, the numbers were small.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Other psychological studies have suggested positive outcome in humans on hormonal therapy but all are weakened by small numbers and their reliance on observations by involved therapists.[56] Reviews stress lack of evidence[57]. It should be emphasised that, unlike older men with cancer whose brains are deteriorating with age, children are being given blockers at a time of great brain development. Moreover, compared to the men whose treatment lasted only months, many children receive blockers for years.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.genderhq.org/trans-youth-side-effects-hormone-blockers-surgery/&quot;&gt;https://www.genderhq.org/trans-youth-side-effects-hormone-blockers-surgery/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This bizarre medical experiment in now taking place, and children in the US and across the world are becoming its victims.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And not for nothing, either. The doctors who perform sex-reassignment surgeries make a fair penny doing it. Doctors are in turn paid by the pharmaceutical companies who make these medications. It is in only within the interest of medical corporations to recommend their own services, and to extoll the supposed benefits. The Philadelphia Center for Transgender Surgery shares a price sheet of surgeries costing thousands, and tens of thousands of dollars, each, for its patients.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thetransgendercenter.com/index.php/mtf-price-list.html&quot;&gt;http://www.thetransgendercenter.com/index.php/mtf-price-list.html&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;One person seeking sex reassignment may receive all, or most, of the surgeries on this list in their lifetime. These costs are in addition to the life-long cost of replacement hormones and doctor visits. The people who seek out this treatment course become permanent patients.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now, the WHO has renamed the disorder again. In it’s eleventh revision of the International Classification of Diseases (ICD-11), “Gender Incongruence” has been defined this way:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“‘a marked and persistent incongruence between the gender felt or experienced and the gender assigned to birth’12. This incongruity is manifested in at least two of the following criteria: - “Strong dislike or disagreement with primary or secondary sexual characteristics due to incongruence with the experienced gender. - “Strong desire to get rid of some of those sexual characteristics due to the incongruence with the experienced gender. - “Strong desire to have the primary or secondary sexual characteristics of the experienced gender. “Strong desire to be treated and accepted as a person of the felt gender.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mentalhealthjournal.org/articles/gender-incongruence-is-no-longer-a-mental-disorder.html&quot;&gt;https://www.mentalhealthjournal.org/articles/gender-incongruence-is-no-longer-a-mental-disorder.html&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Apparently, tho only criteria which can now qualify this diagnosis is a strong desire to become the opposite sex. Soon, everyone who has pondered the notion, or even those who engage in a wistful fantasy, may be convinced of their need for diagnosis. But this can’t be shocking. The definition has simultaneously become so narrow; that it includes only a single symptom of the affor-named “Gender Identity Disorder”; at the same time, its prevalence as a diagnosis increases. The numbers of children referred to gender re-assignment clinics have risen sharply as a result. According to a study published in the Archives of Sexual Behavior:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Over the last decade, several child and adolescent gender identity services have reported an increase in young people who seek help with incongruence between the experienced gender identity and the gender to which they were assigned at birth (Aitken et al., 2015; Wood et al., 2013). Many of those, but not all, would meet the diagnostic criteria for gender dysphoria (GD) (APA, 2013). It has been suggested that this increase is mostly due to an influx of birth-assigned females coming forward.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/324768316_Sex_Ratio_in_Children_and_Adolescents_Referred_to_the_Gender_Identity_Development_Service_in_the_UK_2009-2016&quot;&gt;https://www.researchgate.net/publication/324768316_Sex_Ratio_in_Children_and_Adolescents_Referred_to_the_Gender_Identity_Development_Service_in_the_UK_2009-2016&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Even so, the named authors at the Mental Health Journal proclaim proudly the semantic games of the WHO, having this to say about the final term “Gender Incogruence”:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“On June 18, 2018 the World Health Organization (WHO)5 establish [sic] itself as a pioneer in the process of depathologization of transsexuality. This struggle, in order to stop transsexuality from being considered a mental disorder and to eliminate the gender identity disorder of the international manuals of mental disorders, had been represented in the last decade by the powerful movements of depathologization (Stop Trans Pathologization, depsychopathologisation statement released, etc)6,7,8.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The Manual of International Statistical Classification of Diseases and Related Health Problems (ICD-11) eliminates the term ‘transsexualism’ and replaces it with the term ‘Gender Incongruence ‘ (GI)9. This new terminology will no longer be part of the chapter on mental disorders (chapter 6) but a new chapter is created (chapter 17) called ‘conditions related to sexual health’. These ICD-11 changes implied an advance and a great liberation for trans people who were doubly stigmatized since transsexuality has always been located around paraphilias and within personality disorders.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;When homosexuality was removed from the DSM in 1987, it meant that homosexuals were no longer treated by psychologists. It meant that they were free to live their lives on their own terms, apart from medical and therapeutic intervention — not so with transsexuality. All these definition changes have placed gender identity disorders squarely on the developing edge at the intersection of medicine and psychology. In this case, the “de-psychopathologization” of transsexuality has meant that individuals with gender disorders are receiving more hormones, more surgeries, and more interventions than they ever have. And medical proponents of this plan have practically become the pioneers of a terrifying new field of medicine — one that is not quite plastic surgery, and not quite psychiatry — but somewhere in the middle. It may be the only field of medicine which endeavors to change the body, in order to conform it to the mind.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It begs the question: is this a treatment? Or a program?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Ironically, the authors at the Mental Health Journal reveal the motivations of Radical Trans Rights Activists in their discussion of the initial revisions made to the DSM:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“This first draft didn’t meet the expectations of the trans people that harbored the hope that transsexuality would disappear from the international diagnostic classifications just like it happened with homosexuality11.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What the authors at this journal attribute to “trans people” is better recognized as the strange want of Radical Trans Rights Activists, who have undoubtedly gained influence in the medical community, where they successfully push their agenda. Do not be mistaken: the purpose of this definition change is to normalize the medical transition of children. Removing the diagnosis altogether is the mechanism which intends to permanently normalize transsexuality. The Huffpost author who heralded the end of this war put it bluntly when she said:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Being a patient with a diagnosis implies there’s something wrong with you.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And with that statement, the real intentions of the war are revealed, and the combatants stand in stark relief. As if reeling in the aftermath of an explosion, they are gathered together on each side. They regroup, and do not fear to re-engage. But the enemy is strong. The trumpet of victory was blown too soon. As the author implies, the goal of this movement is not only to “de-psychopathologize”, but even to “de-diagnose” sexual variance — to make it commonplace. And with that, sexual transition will become routine medical care. This is not the war against oppression it figures. This is a war waged by Radical Trans Activists against the sanity of every heterosexual man and woman on the planet. This is the war against gender, as a concept; and sex, as a dimorphic reality. The aim of the Radical Trans Activists who fight in this war is to eliminate, once and for all, men and women. Imagine for a moment: there is no distinction to be made, because none exists. This pictures their utopia.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Perhaps a better name for this war would be: The War Against Our Children.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It is one that cannot continue. We cannot afford to stand idly by while our boys and girls fall victim to this medical machine. This fight can only be fought by Men and Women standing for biological reality. Their agenda can no longer stand up to scrutiny. It dies in the light of information.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/ANIKAHirsch&quot;&gt; /u/ANIKAHirsch &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6ctc/from_gender_identity_disorder_to_gender/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6ctc/from_gender_identity_disorder_to_gender/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_6ctc</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6ctc/from_gender_identity_disorder_to_gender/" /><updated>2020-09-07T18:43:26+00:00</updated><title>From Gender Identity Disorder to Gender Incongruence -- the Normalization of Delusion: OC</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/FediNetizen</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/FediNetizen</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6aly/anatomy_of_a_catastrophe_how_rampant_stupidity/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/1M9LThuAQsk-4JpUWW3UVgfD5XUbuTyndkhmbBrwgmQ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Anatomy of a Catastrophe - How rampant stupidity killed two people in Kenosha&quot; title=&quot;Anatomy of a Catastrophe - How rampant stupidity killed two people in Kenosha&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/FediNetizen&quot;&gt; /u/FediNetizen &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bullshido.net/anatomy-of-a-catastrophe/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6aly/anatomy_of_a_catastrophe_how_rampant_stupidity/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_6aly</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/6aly/anatomy_of_a_catastrophe_how_rampant_stupidity/" /><updated>2020-08-30T20:47:21+00:00</updated><title>Anatomy of a Catastrophe - How rampant stupidity killed two people in Kenosha</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I saw this comment in the AMA thread with Meghan Murphy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;r/IAmA _meghanmurphy1y I am Meghan Murphy, journalist, feminist and founder of Feminist Current. Ask me anything. Journalist&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;hexchromosome wrote:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Age of Entry. Women can virtually always remember at what exact age, what moment of life, they were drawn into a life of prostitution. Among the most important facts established by research is the startlingly young age, at which girls are firstdeceived or forced into prostitution, or driven to it, by homelessness and desperation. This is usually in adolescence, often around the age of 14, 15, or 16.(1) Nothing more clearly refutes the “happy hooker” stereotype than this tragic fact of such a very early age of entering prostitution.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Reference for above: (1). Results differ from one sample to another, and reported statistics are not always comparable. Nonetheless, the basic finding – of a very early age of entry into prostitution – is generally consistent. Nadon et.al.(1998) reported that 89% of the prostituted women they studied had begun before the age of 16. Silbert &amp;amp; Pines (1980, 1982) reported that of 200 women being prostituted in San Francisco, 68% had begun at age 16 or younger. Some of these girls had been 9, 10, 11, or 12 years old. Three studies each reached the same conclusion: an average entry-age of 14: Boyer et al. (1993); Weisberg (1984); Gray (1973). A U.S. government study put the average age of entering prostitution at 12-13 (Spangenberg (2001); http.&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.justice.gov/criminal/ceos/prostitution.html&quot;&gt;www.justice.gov/criminal/ceos/prostitution.html&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Researchers in Seattle (James ,1980, n=136) and in Norway (Høigard &amp;amp; Finstad,1992) each calculated a mean age of entry of 15; James states that 36% of these girls had been 14, or younger. Bagley &amp;amp; Young (1987) found that 51% of prostituted Canadian women they studied had begun at age 15, or younger. A government study of 229 prostituted youth In Canada (1984) determined that they all had entered prostitution between the ages of 8 and 19. Most had been15 to 16, and many had begun at 13 or14.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Childhood Sexual Victimization. Another key fact uncovered by researchers is that 60% to 70% of the women being used in prostitution had previously been victims of sexual abuse or incest in childhood, while still living at home.(2) The magnitude of this relationship astonished those who first discovered it. Sexual abuse was often the direct cause of becoming a run-away, which in turn had led quickly to entrapment in prostitution.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;References for above: (2). Many studies document a strong association between childhood sexual abuse and prostitution, usually beginning in adolescence (Abramovitch, 2005). Ninety percent of the prostituted teenagers studied by Newton-Ruddy &amp;amp; Handelsman (1986) had been sexually abused by care-givers, or neighbors. Some 70% of the prostituted women studied by Silbert and Pines (1982, 1983) said that childhood sexual abuse had played a direct role in their entry to being used in prostitution; 96% of them had been run-aways.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Bagley (1987) reported that 73% of the prostituted women studied had been sexually abused as children. Widom and Kuhns (1996) calculated that girls who are sexually abused are 28 times more likely to later be used in prostitution than are other girls. In a study of children being prostituted in California, most said they had been coerced into prostitution by pimps posing as boyfriends, by friends, classmates, and by men who were strangers to them (Carr, 2009). Girls being prostituted in New York City told researchers they feared and hated the johns, and 87% said they wanted to escape prostitution (Curtis et.al., 2008). Many additional studies verify the startling 60%-70% magnitude of early sexual abuse of women now being used in prostitution: Murphy, 1993; Belton, 1992; Simons &amp;amp; Whitbeck, 1991; Weisberg, 1984; Papery &amp;amp; Deisher, 1983; Farley et.al.,1998; James, 1980; James &amp;amp; Meyerding, 1977. Abuse by older male family members – usually fathers, stepfathers, and foster-fathers – is the most common.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Control by Pimps. Overall percentages are not available, but many careful studies in various locations have determined that 80% to 90% of the girls and women being used in prostitution are notindependent free agents, but are controlled by pimps. (3) Throughout the world, the pimp-sector is basically in daily functional control of prostitution.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;References for above: (3). The Cambodian Women’s Crisis Centre found that 86% of women rescued from Phnom Penh brothels by police had been tricked or sold into prostitution, and did not know they were going to be prostituted, when they left home (Brown, 2000, 66, 89).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The European Union provides data on the extent of pimp-control in a number of European countries (Details in Scelles Foundation, 2012). In Spain, more than 90% of women in prostitution were found to be victims of trafficking by pimps (p.268). In Poland, 90% of prostitution along roads was said to be controlled by organized criminal groups (p.233). In Bulgaria, RiskMonitor estimates that more than 95% of those in prostitution have pimps linked to organized crime (64).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In Germany, a policy analyst estimated that 80%-95% of women in prostitution there have pimps (Barry,1979, p.130).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Percent who Want to Escape From Prostitution. In interviews conducted with 785 prostituted women, in nine different countries, 89% said that they would like to escape prostitution immediately (Farley et.al., 2003).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Reference: Farley, M, et al. (2003) Prostitution and trafficking in nine countries. In Farley, M. (Ed.) Prostitution, Trafficking, and Traumatic Stress. The Haworth Press Inc.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Suicides, and Femicides: In one study, 65% of all prostituted women had been beaten and physically abused by johns (Silbert &amp;amp; Pines,1981). Post Traumatic Stress Disorder in survivors is massive and pervasive; an entire book is devoted to documenting this (Farley,2003). Murders are commonplace. In one year here in New York City, two hundred women being used in prostitution were reported murdered (Rosen, 1981). Such kinds of murders of women can be termed femicides (Russell &amp;amp; Harmes, 2001; Russell &amp;amp; Radford, 1992) . Seventy-five percent of the “call girls” in one study had attempted suicide at least once. Public hospitals have stated that about 15% of all suicide victims are women apparently being used in prostitution (Erbe,1984 ,p. 618-19).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Reference: Erbe, N. (1984). Prostitution: Victims of men’s exploitation and abuse. Law and Inequality, 2, 609.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Boys in Prostitution. Boys are also widely available in prostitution, but less is known, and caution is advisable in generalizing across categories. Homeless boys have been reported to suffer lower levels of sexual trauma than do homeless girls (Gwadz, 2007; Tyler et.al., 2001). Some evidence suggests that boys involved in prostitution may be less often controlled by a pimp than are minor girls or women. For both boys and girls used in prostitution, the buyers are alway adult males, so the situations are not identical. There is a small but growing literature on the use of boys in prostitution.(4)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Reference: Numerous, see article for full description: (4).(Bimbi, 2007, Kaye, 2003, Flowers, 2001, Van Der Poe 1992, Boyer, 1989, Coleman, 1989, Earls &amp;amp; David,1989).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Pornography. Another surprising finding was how deeply intertwined use in prostitution was with making pornography.(5) These two branches of the sex industry overlap indistinguishably, in many ways. Often the same men are involved, using many of the same women. Video pornography is made of girls being used in prostitution, to “prove” their consent, and for blackmail, using a threat of send the films to her parents and relatives (Schwartz et.al., 2007).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;References and info: In one study 38% of women being used in prostitution said they had been used in child pornography before the age of sixteen, 10% of them before the age of thirteen (Silbert &amp;amp; Pines,1982). Pornography in addition harms many other women and men, indirectly, through eroticizing woman-abuse and making it “seem sexy” (Russell, 1991,1993; Brannon, 1991; Layden, 2010; Einseidel, 1991; Brannon &amp;amp; Frank, 1990; Brannon et al., 1996)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5h97/studies_showing_age_of_entry_into_prostitution/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5h97/studies_showing_age_of_entry_into_prostitution/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5h97</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5h97/studies_showing_age_of_entry_into_prostitution/" /><updated>2020-07-17T11:38:26+00:00</updated><title>Studies Showing Age Of Entry Into Prostitution</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.womenarehuman.com/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5g9w/an_independent_source_of_news_stories_relating_to/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5g9w</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5g9w/an_independent_source_of_news_stories_relating_to/" /><updated>2020-07-16T10:51:09+00:00</updated><title>An independent source of news stories relating to gender identity</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5g9f/public_information_and_warning_sexual_offender/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/ebuGPuWyFsEAWt-yU412o7aC10xHiG2bA-dmYFNsw7o.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Public information and warning: sexual offender released&quot; title=&quot;Public information and warning: sexual offender released&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.edmontonpolice.ca/News/MediaReleases/Public%20information%20and%20warning%20about%20sexual%20offender%20released?utm_source=dlvr.it&amp;amp;utm_medium=twitter&amp;amp;fbclid=IwAR3ybQdaD3Ca-k9fG7AUwH3-vAgLPwa7V3iZoA2D7JjyeKBnPWOCZ8arF3M&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5g9f/public_information_and_warning_sexual_offender/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5g9f</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5g9f/public_information_and_warning_sexual_offender/" /><updated>2020-07-16T10:25:58+00:00</updated><title>Public information and warning: sexual offender released</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/joeytundra</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/joeytundra</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/joeytundra&quot;&gt; /u/joeytundra &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://apnews.com/c64e816cac5b0fa1194dd40f576813b2&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5ejl/1994_gay_groups_try_to_put_distance_between/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5ejl</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5ejl/1994_gay_groups_try_to_put_distance_between/" /><updated>2020-07-14T18:59:40+00:00</updated><title>1994- Gay Groups Try to Put Distance Between Themselves and Pedophile Group</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/joeytundra</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/joeytundra</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5eig/boy_scouts_of_america_have_a_pedophile_epidemic/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/w3Yt6VzC23Wo49TLAWmvj-R_qdpdly7sbgcNH0jY890.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Boy Scouts of America have a 'pedophile epidemic' and are hiding hundreds in its ranks, lawyers claim&quot; title=&quot;Boy Scouts of America have a 'pedophile epidemic' and are hiding hundreds in its ranks, lawyers claim&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/joeytundra&quot;&gt; /u/joeytundra &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/boy-scouts-america-have-pedophile-epidemic-are-hiding-hundreds-its-n1039661&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5eig/boy_scouts_of_america_have_a_pedophile_epidemic/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5eig</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5eig/boy_scouts_of_america_have_a_pedophile_epidemic/" /><updated>2020-07-14T18:18:30+00:00</updated><title>Boy Scouts of America have a 'pedophile epidemic' and are hiding hundreds in its ranks, lawyers claim</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cge/transwoman_hannah_mouncey_denied_access_to_womens/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/dDUzsgJ671df0XlHmWXRxEbrSkQW68gDDRgVzJHm8j4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Transwoman Hannah Mouncey Denied Access to Women's Locker Room&quot; title=&quot;Transwoman Hannah Mouncey Denied Access to Women's Locker Room&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://savewomenssports.com/hannah-mouncey&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cge/transwoman_hannah_mouncey_denied_access_to_womens/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5cge</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cge/transwoman_hannah_mouncey_denied_access_to_womens/" /><updated>2020-07-12T11:40:30+00:00</updated><title>Transwoman Hannah Mouncey Denied Access to Women's Locker Room</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cgg/transgender_cyclist_rachel_mckinnon_dominates_as/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/HDi6hJZcLNgLbe5PJbD3WdWKGOnW8WGDLA8JBnYzlW8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Transgender cyclist Rachel McKinnon dominates as competitors cry foul&quot; title=&quot;Transgender cyclist Rachel McKinnon dominates as competitors cry foul&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nypost.com/2019/10/21/transgender-cyclist-rachel-mckinnon-dominates-as-competitors-raise-questions/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cgg/transgender_cyclist_rachel_mckinnon_dominates_as/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5cgg</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cgg/transgender_cyclist_rachel_mckinnon_dominates_as/" /><updated>2020-07-12T11:44:45+00:00</updated><title>Transgender cyclist Rachel McKinnon dominates as competitors cry foul</title></entry><entry><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Original Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TheBurkeanIE/status/1282046735272026113&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/TheBurkeanIE/status/1282046735272026113&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Bitchute Mirror: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitchute.com/video/5gM6kOaexP0n/&quot;&gt;https://www.bitchute.com/video/5gM6kOaexP0n/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cnb/antipaedophilia_protestors_clash_with_antifa/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cnb/antipaedophilia_protestors_clash_with_antifa/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5cnb</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cnb/antipaedophilia_protestors_clash_with_antifa/" /><updated>2020-07-12T17:47:23+00:00</updated><title>Anti-Paedophilia protestors clash with Antifa during #MarchforInnocence</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo2/lesbian_rights_group_banned_from_new_zealand/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/s6CQrYfdJfHRGU8r4rsProOuza1CY4oHRWkg_ebZvU0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lesbian Rights Group banned from New Zealand Pride because the group has no male members – GenderTrending&quot; title=&quot;Lesbian Rights Group banned from New Zealand Pride because the group has no male members – GenderTrending&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2019/03/15/lesbian-rights-group-banned-from-new-zealand-pride-because-the-group-has-no-male-members/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo2/lesbian_rights_group_banned_from_new_zealand/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5bo2</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo2/lesbian_rights_group_banned_from_new_zealand/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:31:04+00:00</updated><title>Lesbian Rights Group banned from New Zealand Pride because the group has no male members – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/nationalistreview</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/nationalistreview</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/nationalistreview&quot;&gt; /u/nationalistreview &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nationalistreview.net/2020/07/12/black-lives-matter-hunts-and-kills-white-mother-after-small-argument/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cao/black_lives_matter_hunts_and_kills_white_mother/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5cao</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cao/black_lives_matter_hunts_and_kills_white_mother/" /><updated>2020-07-12T04:30:19+00:00</updated><title>Black Lives Matter Hunts And Kills White Mother After Small Argument</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfw/transwoman_karen_white_convicted_of_rape/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/OmiVnVMdXZwx55kilx01q6RbG-W4SKFL6w0a96t0jvc.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Transwoman Karen White Convicted Of Rape&quot; title=&quot;Transwoman Karen White Convicted Of Rape&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://transcrimeuk.com/2018/07/17/karen-white/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfw/transwoman_karen_white_convicted_of_rape/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5cfw</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfw/transwoman_karen_white_convicted_of_rape/" /><updated>2020-07-12T11:00:37+00:00</updated><title>Transwoman Karen White Convicted Of Rape</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfu/transwoman_lauren_jeska_convicted_of_attempted/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/OmiVnVMdXZwx55kilx01q6RbG-W4SKFL6w0a96t0jvc.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Transwoman Lauren Jeska Convicted Of Attempted Murder&quot; title=&quot;Transwoman Lauren Jeska Convicted Of Attempted Murder&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://transcrimeuk.com/2017/10/31/lauren-jeska/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfu/transwoman_lauren_jeska_convicted_of_attempted/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5cfu</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfu/transwoman_lauren_jeska_convicted_of_attempted/" /><updated>2020-07-12T10:56:21+00:00</updated><title>Transwoman Lauren Jeska Convicted Of Attempted Murder</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/joeytundra</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/joeytundra</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/joeytundra&quot;&gt; /u/joeytundra &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dallasnews.com/opinion/editorials/2019/12/18/a-ut-professor-advocates-pedophilia-why-are-we-paying-for-it/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5ceg/cancel_culture_doesnt_apply_to_pedophile/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5ceg</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5ceg/cancel_culture_doesnt_apply_to_pedophile/" /><updated>2020-07-12T08:49:43+00:00</updated><title>Cancel Culture doesn't apply to pedophile professors.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.feministcurrent.com/2019/05/02/stonewall-has-sold-out-lesbians-and-its-time-they-be-held-to-account/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cg0/stonewall_has_sold_out_lesbians_and_its_time_they/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5cg0</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cg0/stonewall_has_sold_out_lesbians_and_its_time_they/" /><updated>2020-07-12T11:06:42+00:00</updated><title>Stonewall has sold out lesbians and it’s time they be held to account</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.skepticat.org/2017/09/when-vicious-entitled-thugs-attack-i-fight-back/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cgb/maria_maclachlan_speaks_about_assault_by/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5cgb</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cgb/maria_maclachlan_speaks_about_assault_by/" /><updated>2020-07-12T11:35:11+00:00</updated><title>Maria MacLachlan Speaks About Assault By Transactivist</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bn4/media_blackout_on_dana_rivers_michfest_murder/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/FV1sK5i5loptL8AuVM_du0hrRI-mZ7eBLXIN5WAUlE0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Media Blackout on Dana Rivers “Michfest” Murder Trial – GenderTrending&quot; title=&quot;Media Blackout on Dana Rivers “Michfest” Murder Trial – GenderTrending&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2019/08/13/media-blackout-on-dana-rivers-michfest-murder-trial/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bn4/media_blackout_on_dana_rivers_michfest_murder/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5bn4</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bn4/media_blackout_on_dana_rivers_michfest_murder/" /><updated>2020-07-11T11:53:10+00:00</updated><title>Media Blackout on Dana Rivers “Michfest” Murder Trial – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfy/transwoman_tanis_wolf_tara_wood_convicted_of/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/OmiVnVMdXZwx55kilx01q6RbG-W4SKFL6w0a96t0jvc.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Transwoman Tanis Wolf / Tara Wood Convicted Of Assault Of Maria MacLachlan&quot; title=&quot;Transwoman Tanis Wolf / Tara Wood Convicted Of Assault Of Maria MacLachlan&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://transcrimeuk.com/2018/01/24/tanis-wolf-tara-wood/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfy/transwoman_tanis_wolf_tara_wood_convicted_of/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5cfy</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfy/transwoman_tanis_wolf_tara_wood_convicted_of/" /><updated>2020-07-12T11:03:23+00:00</updated><title>Transwoman Tanis Wolf / Tara Wood Convicted Of Assault Of Maria MacLachlan</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cft/trans_crime_uk_archive/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/6E0YXUncXhFZE-HgC8IH7COjePvS20nr4P30WrcpyiU.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Trans Crime UK Archive&quot; title=&quot;Trans Crime UK Archive&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://transcrimeuk.com/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cft/trans_crime_uk_archive/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5cft</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cft/trans_crime_uk_archive/" /><updated>2020-07-12T10:55:00+00:00</updated><title>Trans Crime UK Archive</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2017/02/12/transactivists-vandalize-destroy-books-and-harass-feminists-at-the-vancouver-womens-library/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnp/transactivists_vandalize_destroy_books_and_harass/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bnp</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnp/transactivists_vandalize_destroy_books_and_harass/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:22:19+00:00</updated><title>Transactivists vandalize, destroy books, and harass feminists at the Vancouver Womens Library – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo5/maamsplaining_gendertrending/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/XZjcpHF6jHGhktA1NzSSfTrgISMPyfneNjXrckgg5p4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ma’amsplaining – GenderTrending&quot; title=&quot;Ma’amsplaining – GenderTrending&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2019/06/07/maamsplaining/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo5/maamsplaining_gendertrending/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5bo5</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo5/maamsplaining_gendertrending/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:33:03+00:00</updated><title>Ma’amsplaining – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2013/03/30/there-is-no-such-thing-as-a-pregnant-man-rules-arizona-judge-in-thomas-beatie-case/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnl/there_is_no_such_thing_as_a_pregnant_man_rules/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bnl</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnl/there_is_no_such_thing_as_a_pregnant_man_rules/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:12:56+00:00</updated><title>There is no such thing as a pregnant man rules Arizona judge in Thomas Beatie case – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5boh/a_new_way_to_be_mad/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/4gvt4hFRNU1vbuW-fWVxcKWx_My_wteLHndDdr9s_-4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A New Way to Be Mad&quot; title=&quot;A New Way to Be Mad&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2000/12/a-new-way-to-be-mad/304671/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5boh/a_new_way_to_be_mad/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5boh</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5boh/a_new_way_to_be_mad/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:49:33+00:00</updated><title>A New Way to Be Mad</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfs/002_1855_joe_rogan_reflects_on_fallon_fox/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/TKwpoAfJeOS3KM3SxOH5-HHWowtDiuUMwuCx1rD1ZXc.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;0:02 / 18:55 Joe Rogan Reflects on Fallon Fox Controversy&quot; title=&quot;0:02 / 18:55 Joe Rogan Reflects on Fallon Fox Controversy&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KQpQmNhya14&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfs/002_1855_joe_rogan_reflects_on_fallon_fox/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5cfs</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfs/002_1855_joe_rogan_reflects_on_fallon_fox/" /><updated>2020-07-12T10:50:52+00:00</updated><title>0:02 / 18:55 Joe Rogan Reflects on Fallon Fox Controversy</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfo/this_trans_woman_kept_her_beard_and_couldnt_be/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/O4OPpk9I_RkaWRTvRmlumO72unwC-6NJ7sBlbpP4NRk.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;This Trans Woman Kept Her Beard And Couldn't Be Happier&quot; title=&quot;This Trans Woman Kept Her Beard And Couldn't Be Happier&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.buzzfeed.com/patrickstrudwick/this-transgender-woman-has-a-full-beard-and-she-couldnt-be-h&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfo/this_trans_woman_kept_her_beard_and_couldnt_be/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5cfo</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5cfo/this_trans_woman_kept_her_beard_and_couldnt_be/" /><updated>2020-07-12T10:35:17+00:00</updated><title>This Trans Woman Kept Her Beard And Couldn't Be Happier</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2011/08/27/mom-to-georgia-elementary-school-im-a-man-and-so-is-my-7-year-old-daughter/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bne/mom_to_georgia_elementary_school_im_a_man_and_so/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bne</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bne/mom_to_georgia_elementary_school_im_a_man_and_so/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:03:31+00:00</updated><title>Mom to Georgia Elementary School: I’m a Man. And so is my 7 year-old Daughter. – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.is/DI3rz&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bob/stefonknee_wolscht_the_middle_aged_transgirl/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bob</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bob/stefonknee_wolscht_the_middle_aged_transgirl/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:41:18+00:00</updated><title>Stefonknee Wolscht, The Middle Aged &quot;Transgirl&quot;</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2011/03/04/men-love-the-ladies-restroom-this-week-in-the-news/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bn6/men_love_the_ladies_restroom_this_week_in_the/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bn6</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bn6/men_love_the_ladies_restroom_this_week_in_the/" /><updated>2020-07-11T11:56:11+00:00</updated><title>Men Love the Ladies Restroom- This Week In The News – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2018/10/20/trans-activists-smoke-bomb-uk-newspaper-offices-in-gender-recognition-terror-attack/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bn3/trans_activists_smoke_bomb_uk_newspaper_offices/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bn3</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bn3/trans_activists_smoke_bomb_uk_newspaper_offices/" /><updated>2020-07-11T11:50:47+00:00</updated><title>Trans Activists Smoke Bomb UK Newspaper Offices In Gender Recognition Terror Attack – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2017/09/14/this-is-trans-terrorism-this-is-male-violence/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnr/this_is_trans_terrorism_this_is_male_violence/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bnr</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnr/this_is_trans_terrorism_this_is_male_violence/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:23:30+00:00</updated><title>This Is Trans Terrorism. This Is Male Violence. – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2013/11/20/transgender-activists-plan-protest-against-day-of-remembrance-for-women-murdered-in-the-lecole-polytechnique-massacre/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnm/transgender_activists_plan_protest_against_day_of/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bnm</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnm/transgender_activists_plan_protest_against_day_of/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:15:15+00:00</updated><title>Transgender Activists plan protest against Day of Remembrance for Women Murdered in the L’Ecole Polytechnique Massacre – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2011/07/07/ftm-detransitioner-the-subcultural-pressure-on-young-women-to-medically-transition/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnc/ftm_detransitioner_the_subcultural_pressure_on/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bnc</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnc/ftm_detransitioner_the_subcultural_pressure_on/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:01:27+00:00</updated><title>FTM Detransitioner : The Subcultural Pressure On Young Women To Medically “Transition” – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo7/courtroom_play_by_play_of_jonathan_yanivs/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/yJxFvDQ45piUYM13RXSiM_0hqOMGUggbuGx7XE5RDGQ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Courtroom Play by Play of Jonathan Yaniv’s #WaxMyBalls Tribunal – GenderTrending&quot; title=&quot;Courtroom Play by Play of Jonathan Yaniv’s #WaxMyBalls Tribunal – GenderTrending&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2019/07/07/courtroom-play-by-play-of-jonathan-yanivs-waxmyballs-tribunal/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo7/courtroom_play_by_play_of_jonathan_yanivs/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5bo7</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo7/courtroom_play_by_play_of_jonathan_yanivs/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:34:49+00:00</updated><title>Courtroom Play by Play of Jonathan Yaniv’s #WaxMyBalls Tribunal – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2011/09/06/who-are-the-males-who-sneak-into-michigan-womens-music-festival/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnj/who_are_the_males_who_sneak_into_michigan_womyns/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bnj</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnj/who_are_the_males_who_sneak_into_michigan_womyns/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:10:18+00:00</updated><title>Who Are The Males Who Sneak Into Michigan Womyn's Music Festival? – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2018/04/27/san-francisco-public-library-hosts-transgender-art-exhibit-featuring-weapons-intended-to-kill-feminists/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnt/san_francisco_public_library_hosts_transgender/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bnt</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnt/san_francisco_public_library_hosts_transgender/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:25:29+00:00</updated><title>San Francisco Public Library hosts transgender “art exhibit” featuring weapons intended to kill feminists – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo6/on_the_heels_of_the_jonathan_yaniv_saga_another/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/WPC_q_DBL9U9Pg627hy2SEntM7RrmsjQnMvsKXkPHdQ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;On the heels of the Jonathan Yaniv saga: Another Crazy BC Human Rights Tribunal Case – GenderTrending&quot; title=&quot;On the heels of the Jonathan Yaniv saga: Another Crazy BC Human Rights Tribunal Case – GenderTrending&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2019/07/28/on-the-heels-of-the-jonathan-yaniv-saga-another-crazy-bc-human-rights-tribunal-case/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo6/on_the_heels_of_the_jonathan_yaniv_saga_another/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5bo6</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo6/on_the_heels_of_the_jonathan_yaniv_saga_another/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:33:49+00:00</updated><title>On the heels of the Jonathan Yaniv saga: Another Crazy BC Human Rights Tribunal Case – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo4/declaration_on_womens_sex_based_rights/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/brVbCJlZaRf1fIkCxHsR3azgwEyGesEP-5KtOcdUBNM.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Declaration on Women’s Sex Based Rights – GenderTrending&quot; title=&quot;Declaration on Women’s Sex Based Rights – GenderTrending&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2019/03/13/declaration-on-womens-sex-based-rights/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo4/declaration_on_womens_sex_based_rights/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5bo4</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo4/declaration_on_womens_sex_based_rights/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:31:48+00:00</updated><title>Declaration on Women’s Sex Based Rights – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo0/fascinating_account_by_miranda_yardley_the_first/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/blMmfApKpsGHcf2mvNVKxtcBBx2MjWuF61JLbDdVk48.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fascinating account by Miranda Yardley, the first transsexual to be prosecuted for “transphobia” – GenderTrending&quot; title=&quot;Fascinating account by Miranda Yardley, the first transsexual to be prosecuted for “transphobia” – GenderTrending&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2019/03/18/fascinating-account-by-miranda-yardley-the-first-transsexual-to-be-prosecuted-for-transphobia/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo0/fascinating_account_by_miranda_yardley_the_first/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_5bo0</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bo0/fascinating_account_by_miranda_yardley_the_first/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:30:18+00:00</updated><title>Fascinating account by Miranda Yardley, the first transsexual to be prosecuted for “transphobia” – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2011/05/28/men-love-the-ladies-restroom-transgender-edition/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bn7/men_love_the_ladies_restroom_transgender_edition/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bn7</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bn7/men_love_the_ladies_restroom_transgender_edition/" /><updated>2020-07-11T11:58:08+00:00</updated><title>Men Love The Ladies Restroom- Transgender Edition – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2018/07/30/first-elected-nus-trans-officer-jess-bradley-suspended-under-investigation-for-alleged-public-flashing-indecent-exposure/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnx/first_elected_nus_trans_officer_jess_bradley/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bnx</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnx/first_elected_nus_trans_officer_jess_bradley/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:28:28+00:00</updated><title>First elected NUS Trans Officer Jess Bradley suspended under investigation for alleged public flashing, indecent exposure – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2012/02/01/national-geographic-taboo-fake-paraplegic-chloe-jennings-white/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bng/national_geographics_taboo_fake_paraplegic_chloe/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bng</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bng/national_geographics_taboo_fake_paraplegic_chloe/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:07:24+00:00</updated><title>National Geographic's &quot;Taboo&quot; : Fake paraplegic Chloe Jennings-White – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2014/08/22/laverne-cox-launches-media-campaign-in-support-of-transwoman-synthia-china-blast-convicted-for-the-rape-murder-and-abuse-of-the-corpse-of-thirteen-year-old-ebony-nicole-williams/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnn/laverne_cox_launches_media_campaign_in_support_of/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bnn</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnn/laverne_cox_launches_media_campaign_in_support_of/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:19:42+00:00</updated><title>LAVERNE COX LAUNCHES MEDIA CAMPAIGN IN SUPPORT OF TRANSWOMAN SYNTHIA CHINA BLAST: CONVICTED FOR THE RAPE, MURDER AND ABUSE OF THE CORPSE OF THIRTEEN-YEAR-OLD EBONY NICOLE WILLIAMS</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2013/02/11/trans-woman-student-abused-and-shoved-out-of-toilets-at-leeds-university/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnk/trans_woman_student_abused_and_shoved_out_of/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bnk</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnk/trans_woman_student_abused_and_shoved_out_of/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:11:54+00:00</updated><title>&quot;Trans Woman student Abused and Shoved out of toilets at Leeds University&quot; – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2017/12/13/watch-here-the-transgender-kids-documentary-banned-tonight-from-the-cbc/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bns/watch_here_the_transgender_kids_documentary/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bns</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bns/watch_here_the_transgender_kids_documentary/" /><updated>2020-07-11T12:24:35+00:00</updated><title>Watch here: the &quot;Transgender Kids&quot; documentary *BANNED* tonight from the CBC – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gendertrending.com/2011/07/29/jezebel-headline-female-adult-baby-wears-diapers-247/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnb/jezebel_headline_female_adult_baby_wears_diapers/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_5bnb</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/5bnb/jezebel_headline_female_adult_baby_wears_diapers/" /><updated>2020-07-11T11:59:56+00:00</updated><title>Jezebel Headline: &quot;Female Adult Baby Wears Diapers 24/7&quot; – GenderTrending</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Susiesmum</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Susiesmum&quot;&gt; /u/Susiesmum &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.is/XVLl1&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/549q/archive_of_gender_critical_peak_trans_threads/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t5_549q</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/549q/archive_of_gender_critical_peak_trans_threads/" /><updated>2020-07-01T12:31:35+00:00</updated><title>Archive of Gender critical Peak Trans Threads</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Robin</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Robin</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/3vp7/life_under_quarantine/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/ROPCQoHto4bHFNXPRAMltZaDSc_iylwXZeNw6QhxfnY.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Life under quarantine&quot; title=&quot;Life under quarantine&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Robin&quot;&gt; /u/Robin &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://wikispooks.com/w/images/thumb/8/8e/Reddit_censorship_911_truth.jpg/505px-Reddit_censorship_911_truth.jpg&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/3vp7/life_under_quarantine/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_3vp7</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/3vp7/life_under_quarantine/" /><updated>2020-04-16T05:17:14+00:00</updated><title>Life under quarantine</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/seanspeaks</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/seanspeaks</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/3syj/freedomgate_2_years_of_research_exposing_the_new/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/C6efiOmUDNQb56gd4PoJgQ79PTrZ9DZT-KG6UaG-O40.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;FREEDOMGATE: 2 years of research exposing The New World Order Agenda and all the LIES fed to the public about Main Historical Events. Available as PDF download or video format.&quot; title=&quot;FREEDOMGATE: 2 years of research exposing The New World Order Agenda and all the LIES fed to the public about Main Historical Events. Available as PDF download or video format.&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greatings fellow said-iters! Im new here so go easy on me... I would like to take this opportunity to present to you my creation which is Freedomgate... Enjoy and please lets me know your thoughts! :)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What is Freedom Gate?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Freedom Gate is my creation. Its basically an accumulation of videos and presentations I&amp;#39;ve put together to expose the ruling elite or new world order agenda on planet earth. I have dedicated my life to unraveling this concept to determine if its real or if its just a theory. I can conclusively tell you at the age of 26 that the new world order really does exist, evil people are controlling world affairs and everything that happens in our world benefits the 1% of the population and not the 99%. If we don&amp;#39;t take action and do something soon they are going to take all our rights and freedoms away with this coronavirus outbreak by indicting martial law. They are just getting us use to the idea of a militarised police state but eventually it will become permanent. A totalitarian world government that only benefits the people at the top whilst the rest of us are tagged and quarantined with radio frequency identity tags to make us easier to control.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;THE POWER OF THE PEOPLE IS STRONGER THAN THE PEOPLE IN POWER.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I have spent the last 2 years of my life putting solid, hardcore and factual information together that proves we have been lied to about all main historical events. What makes you think this coronavirus outbreak is any different? If we don&amp;#39;t take action and stand up for ourselves were all screwed. Its the events of the past and action of our governments that have shaped the present. We must understand the events of the past if we are ever to understand why the world is the way it is today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;THE TIME TO ACT IS NOW&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;First watch my introductory video on freedomgate = &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RoZj8JCgk0o&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RoZj8JCgk0o&lt;/a&gt; Freedom Gate is split into 7 categories:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1 = PIZZAGATE&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2 = THE 5G NETWORK IS THE PHYSICAL MANIFESTATION OF THE NEW WORLD ORDER AGENDA&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3 = TRUTHGATE&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART 1 = WHAT IS ALTERNATIVE NEWS PART 2 = 911 (PARTS 1-3) PART 3 = THE TRUTH ABOUT THE WARS IN THE MIDDLE EAST PART 4 = WHO REALLY CONTROLS THE WORLD&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4 = ASCENSIONGATE&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5 = IRISGATE&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6= CORRUPTIONGATE&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;7 = MEDIAGATE&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Breakdown of my work available as PDF or videos.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PIZZGATE Pizzagate is real. my presentations prove that there is enough evidence for law enforcement to open up an investigation. Please look at the material in your own time.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART 1 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_VKNxHpRSO0&amp;amp;t=6573s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_VKNxHpRSO0&amp;amp;t=6573s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - John Podesta&amp;#39;s Creepy Emails 09:53 - John and Tony Podesta 21:12 - Comet Ping Pong/Pizza 39:39- James Alefantis - Jimmy Commet Instagram Profile 01:26:24 - Wherkinonmahnightcheese Instagram Profile - CHILD SIZED COFFINS 01:28:29 - Pegasus Museum - Location of The Kill Room 01:42:12 - Underground Tunnels 01:49:43 - Pegasus Museum - Amos Connection - Child Sacrifice Worship pizzagate part 1 pdf download = &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mediafire.com/file/jc5qvvjpemhbqpm/PART_1_-_The_Truth_About_Pizzagate_%2528Killing_Children%2529.pdf/file&quot;&gt;http://www.mediafire.com/file/jc5qvvjpemhbqpm/PART_1_-_The_Truth_About_Pizzagate_%2528Killing_Children%2529.pdf/file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART2 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GtE-WpMhjfo&amp;amp;t=5636s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GtE-WpMhjfo&amp;amp;t=5636s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - James Alefantis Threatens To Kill Researcher (Ryan O&amp;#39;neill) For Kill Room Video 10:14 - The Dark Truth - Child Torture 16:00 - Paedophile Symbols Known To The FBI 42:41 - Beyond Borders - Clinton Foundation 48:42 - Laura Silsby - Convicted Child Trafficker Saved By The Clinton Mafia 57:16 - Anthony Weiner, Hume Abedin, Hilary Clinton Connection 01:03:50 - Seth Rich 01:15:52 - Huma Abedins Connection To The Muslim Brotherhood - How The West Created Extremist Ideologies To Promote Violence Worldwide pizzagate part 2 pdf download = &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mediafire.com/file/vkwn4mfxtrbxylx/PART_2_-_The_Truth_About_Pizzagate_%2528Killing_Children%2529.pdf/file&quot;&gt;http://www.mediafire.com/file/vkwn4mfxtrbxylx/PART_2_-_The_Truth_About_Pizzagate_%2528Killing_Children%2529.pdf/file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART 3 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6tULHUwKjMQ&amp;amp;t=3s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6tULHUwKjMQ&amp;amp;t=3s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - How The UK and Western Nations Fund Terrorism 48:50 - Conclusion on Huma Abedin&amp;#39;s Connections With The Muslim Brotherhood 01:02:54 - Jeffery Epstein, The Clintons and Orgy Island 01:18:27 - FBI Anonymous 01:27:37 - The Washington DC Spider Web pizzagate part 3 pdf download = &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mediafire.com/file/qupuqfta30oeyde/PART_3_-_The_Truth_About_Pizzagate_%2528Killing_Children%2529.pdf/file&quot;&gt;http://www.mediafire.com/file/qupuqfta30oeyde/PART_3_-_The_Truth_About_Pizzagate_%2528Killing_Children%2529.pdf/file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART 4 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iZjLxSArk7M&amp;amp;t=1820s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iZjLxSArk7M&amp;amp;t=1820s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - James Alefantis&amp;#39;s Powerful Connections in Washington DC 02:50 - James Alefantis, Coded Language, Symbolism and Occult Hidden Messages 27:53 - James Alefantis and Marina Abrovamich Connection 01:00:23 - Thought Provoking Truth - The Elite Power Structure on Planet Earth 01:11:40 - THE POWER OF THE PEOPLE IS STRONGER THAN THE PEOPLE IN POWER 01:26:13 - Obvious Media Cover Up of Pizzagate 01:36:35 - &amp;quot;Fake News&amp;quot; term Was Created By The Media Because Of The Pizzagate Scandal Final pizzagate download = &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mediafire.com/file/kvshowp8uk9qpqc/PART_4_-_The_Truth_About_Pizzagate_%2528Killing_Children%2529.pdf/file&quot;&gt;http://www.mediafire.com/file/kvshowp8uk9qpqc/PART_4_-_The_Truth_About_Pizzagate_%2528Killing_Children%2529.pdf/file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART 5 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oEj9W9IL9-c&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oEj9W9IL9-c&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - Hacker &amp;quot;Big Fish&amp;quot; Finds Child Porn Hidden on Comet Pizza Servers 3:00 - Commet Pizza False Flag Shooting 8:25 - Crisis Actors 25:01 - Hacker &amp;quot;Big Fish&amp;quot; Reports Findings To FBI + Hidden Blockchain Network Found On Comet Pizza Severs For Elite Individuals 37:11 - Palintir - Quin Michaels Research 45:58 Pizzagate Death Threats To Credible Researchers Trying To Expose This Scandal 47:55 - Silencing Ben Swann 49:05 - How The CIA Procure Children For The Elite 55:31 - Potential Video of John Pedestal Abusing a Child 01:05:08 - DEMAND A NON-BIAS LAW ENFORCEMENT INVESTIGATION INTO PIZZAGATE IMMEDIATELY WHICH IS OPEN TO PUBLIC SCRUTINY AND INVOLVEMENT 02:12:00 - What Needs To Happen Next&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART 6 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QM68PS8MTbg&amp;amp;t=1s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QM68PS8MTbg&amp;amp;t=1s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - Pizzagate Special Mentions 06:51 - Robertos Pizza and Its Connections 29:18 - Marina Abromovich - Random Acts Connection&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The 5G NETWORK IS THE PHYSICAL MANIFESTATION OF THE NEW WORLD ORDER AGENDA&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5G PDF DOWNLOAD &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mediafire.com/file/k8zmqq7izinaowh/5G_-_GATE.pdf/file&quot;&gt;http://www.mediafire.com/file/k8zmqq7izinaowh/5G_-_GATE.pdf/file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART 1 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BttIfD-WzGg&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BttIfD-WzGg&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - 5G Intro 11:10 - Microwave Warefare 19:38 - Radar + Radiation 27:06 - The 5G Infrastructure 37:43 - 5G and Chemtrails 48:07 - Leaked Nasa Document (The War of The Future Will Be Between The Government and The People) 53:24 - Chemtrails and Morgellons Connection 59:54 - The 5G Network Is The Foundation For The Internet of Things (IOT) 01:12:37 - Cashless Society, Contactless Payments, and Radio Frequency Identity Tags (RFID) Chipping Agenda&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART 2 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_4X-emskJ3I&amp;amp;t=1s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_4X-emskJ3I&amp;amp;t=1s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - The Internet of Things, Radio Frequency Identity Tags (RFID) and The Migration To Totally Digital Bank Accounts 05:30 - Artificial Intelligence 09:50 - How Technology Is Passed Down To The Masses 15:15 - The Secret Space Programme Connection 19:08 - Brief History of The Secret Space Programme 24:15 - Operation Highjump 28:18 - Admiral Byrd Granted Passage Into Hollow Earth 33:33 - Washington DC UFO Incident 34:40 - Operation Paperclip 39:35 - Conclusion On Where Artificial Intelligence Came From 40:07 - Artificial Intelligence and War 42:42 - Artificial Intelligence, 5G and The Internet of Things Connection 46:18 - Artificial Intelligence Conclusion 48:48 - The Space Fence 01:02:38 - Who Is Behind The 5G Rollout? 01:05:40 - 5G Network Giants - Vodafone and Telefonica&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART 3 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2DJQp9h40Ek&amp;amp;t=3s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2DJQp9h40Ek&amp;amp;t=3s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - World Health Organisations View On Health Risks Associated With Electromagnetic Field (EMF) Exposure 07:10 - Telefonicas View On On Health Risks Associated With Electromagnetic Field (EMF) Exposure 13:13 - Cornerstone Telecommunications Infrastructure Limited (CTIL) 25:15 - International Commission On Non-Ionizing Radiation Protection (ICNIRP) 54:37 - The Case of Eileen Cooper 56:56 - Human Health Effects of EMF: The Cost of Doing Nothing&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART 4 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nl2SGKYt1Ts&amp;amp;t=110s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nl2SGKYt1Ts&amp;amp;t=110s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - Microwaving The World: The Electromagnetic Pollution 1:34 - 7 Ways EMF Technology Seriously Threatens Entire Populations 3:30 - Frequency 05:50 - Transhumanism 11:52 - The Synthetic Agenda 32:32 - Artificial Intelligence Used In The Telecommunication Industry 34:45 - Stop Stingray Surveillance 38:45 - The True Dangers of Airport Security Scanners 50:13 - Accountability&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TRUTHGATE&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PART 1 = WHAT IS ALTERNATIVE NEWS? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zPl_laOv7As&amp;amp;t=3792s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zPl_laOv7As&amp;amp;t=3792s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - Truthgate Introduction 04:16 - What Is Alternative News? 07:44 - PROBLEM - REACTION - SOLUTION - Explained 14:28 - Okay So, Ive Made An Archeological Discovery... 17:36 - The Vatican Has 54 MILES of Forbidden Archives Underground. This Is Where They Hide Advanced Technology And Ancient Artefacts About The Origin of The Human Race And Our Cosmic Heritage. 19:27 - Vaccines 20:59 - Genetically Modified Foods 22:09 - Fukushima 29:25 - False Flags PDF = &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mediafire.com/file/u58bnvsxugo33hz/TRUTHGATE_-_ALTERNATIVE_NEWS.pdf/file&quot;&gt;http://www.mediafire.com/file/u58bnvsxugo33hz/TRUTHGATE_-_ALTERNATIVE_NEWS.pdf/file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TRUTHGATE PART 2 = 911 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OCP3Leq3qjI&amp;amp;t=1366s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OCP3Leq3qjI&amp;amp;t=1366s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - Is 911 The Biggest False Flag in History? YOU DECIDE 06:49 - No Warnings 10:28 - 19 -Highjackers? 15:38 - Osama Bin Laden - A CIA Assett 19:58 - The Pentagon Missile 24:50 - Shanksville Flight 93 - A Hole In The Ground 27:50 - World Trade Centres - Pre 911 30:31 - World Trade Centres Structural Support 34:52 - World Trade Centre Elevators 36:48 - The Bath Tub - Water Tight Seal Built Into The Foundations 39:18 - World Trade Centre Construction 41:12 - September 11th 2001 41:55 - Pancake Theory - A Think Tank Creation To Conceal Which Was Obviously a Demolition 48:22 - Buildings Free Fall Collapse Into Its Own Footprint 56:51 - True Volume of Jet Fuel In Each Plane 01:02:38 - Federal Emergency Management Agency - FEMA 01:05:33 - What Is Jet Fuel? + Jet Fuel Only Burns When You Atomize It 01:08:53 - The Towers Empty Floors - Derelict Buildings 01:12:41 - Safety Measures Against Fires 01:16:33 - World Trade Centre Sprinkler System - 55,000 GALLONS OF WATER A MINUTE. 01:26:37 - Building Fire Examples - No Building Has Collapsed The Same As The Twin Towers Did Before Or After 911. 01:34:32 - A Plane Crashed Into The Empire State Building In 1945 - IT DIDNT COLLAPSE 01:36:54 - Fire Does Not Melt Steel 01:39:53 - Floor Trusses - THEY WERE NOT WEAK&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;911 PART 2.1 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t90GYu9vlHA&amp;amp;t=2100s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t90GYu9vlHA&amp;amp;t=2100s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - Debunking The Floor Truss Theory Continued 2:37 - Controlled Demolition And Explosives - THE EVIDENCE 12:19 - Molten Steel + Thermite (An Explosive Compound) 23:15 - Lasagne Steel + Glowing Red Steel Cover Up 25:12 - A BOMB THAT FAILED TO DETONATE FOUND AT GROUND ZERO 33:16 - THE NEW WORLD ORDER - FACT NOT FICTION 44:49 - Sub Basement And Other Explosions Before Plane Strike 01:07:34 - Testimony of David Long - Eye Witness 01:15:29 - Fire Fighters - Explosions - Explosive Testimonies 01:30:47 - Sabotage of Elevators - RIGGED WITH BOMBS 02:08:35 - Office And Basement Explosions 02:10:26 Sabotage of Emergency Back Up Generators - RIGGED WITH BOMBS&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;911 PART 2.2 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y8ljJDn6uos&amp;amp;t=10s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y8ljJDn6uos&amp;amp;t=10s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - World Trade Centre Complex 2:40 - Operations Command Centre (OCC) - Evacuated Early 04:58 - Secret Security Command Centre (SCC) + Mechanical Equipment Rooms BOMBED 17:54 - Power Cut Off To Elevators 19:34 - A Firefighters Worst Nightmare 30:00 - The South Tower - DEMOLITION 37:06 - The North Tower - DEMOLITION 44:36 - Visible Smoke At Bottom of Towers From Basement Explosions 45:35 - Ground Zero 52:40 - WTC Cover Up - Controlled Demolition Inc. 01:00:21 - Profiting From 911 - SAIC 01:20:42 - Turner Construction 01:23:17 - Manhattan Demolition Truck Seen On 911 01:26:10 - Mark Dayton Lied About 911 01:28:00 - NORAD JET FIGHTERS DEPLOYED OVER 200 MILES FROM NEW YORK ON 911 01:30:13 - NORAD And Dick Cheney 01:37:03 - Hijacked Planes Flew Directly Over American Air Force Bases Without Causing Any Suspicion? 01:39:50 - Operation Northwood - PROBLEM - REACTION - SOLUTION 01:42:32 - The Truth About MALAYSIAN FLIGHT MH370&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;911 PART 2.3 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c9z9kh9v8j4&amp;amp;t=807s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c9z9kh9v8j4&amp;amp;t=807s&lt;/a&gt; 0:00 - Convar - PROOF INSIDER TRADING TOOK PLACE ON 911 - $100 MILLION DOLLARS TRANSFERRED MINUTES BEFORE THE DETONATION 07:21 - 911 Key Witnessed And Activists Who Were Silenced 38:20- Evidence of NO PLANES Hitting The Towers (Parts 1-4) 40:05 - NO PLANES - PART 1 - 4 Separate Videos Showing Towers Just Exploding - NO PLANES. 42:05 - NO PLANES - PART 2 - Wing Goes Behind Building - CGI ERROR 42:39 - NO PLANES - PART 3 - Testimony of John Lear - EX CIA PILOT 01:07:11 - NO PLANES - PART 3 - Every Plane Has Unique Serial Numbers On All Its Parts - No Part Has Ever Been Proven To Be From Any Alleged Plane Used On 911 - THE GOVERNMENT HAS KEPT THE ID NUMBERS SECRET FOR 19 YEARS - WHY? 01:15:26 - Architects + Engineers For 911 Truth 01:17:00 - Building 7 - Purposely Omitted From The 911 Report 01:23:07 - NIST Didn&amp;#39;t Find Any Evidence For Explosives - THATS BECAUSE NIST DIDNT TEST FOR EXPLOSIVES - HOW CAN YOU SAY THERE IS NO EVIDENCE FOR EXPLOSIVES IF YOU DIDNT EVEN TEST FOR EXPLOSIVES? 01:28:55 - Building 7 Continued - SINGLE COLLUM COLLAPSE? 01:41:32 - Freedom Of Information Images Released 14 Years Later - PROVE BOMBS WERE PLANTED BELOW THE IMPACT HOLE. DOWNLOAD ALL 911 PDF HERE: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mediafire.com/file/t5ixbiqj7veku4z/TRUTHGATE_-_911_-_PART_1_-_CORRECT_VERSION.pdf/file&quot;&gt;http://www.mediafire.com/file/t5ixbiqj7veku4z/TRUTHGATE_-_911_-_PART_1_-_CORRECT_VERSION.pdf/file&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mediafire.com/file/wy2p62kmef5ycvc/TRUTHGATE_-_911_PART_2.pdf/file&quot;&gt;http://www.mediafire.com/file/wy2p62kmef5ycvc/TRUTHGATE_-_911_PART_2.pdf/file&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mediafire.com/file/w7tq3edsdt593n6/TRUTHGATE_-_911_PART_3.pdf/file&quot;&gt;http://www.mediafire.com/file/w7tq3edsdt593n6/TRUTHGATE_-_911_PART_3.pdf/file&lt;/a&gt; There is more content in my PDFS. My videos are being taken down on youtube and showing as &amp;quot;error 404&amp;quot; on bit chute.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TRUTHGATE PART 3 = THE TRUTH ABOUT THE WARS IN THE MIDDLE EAST DOWNLOAD MIDDLE EAST PDF HERE: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mediafire.com/file/v4wz4t7c3j8dh2n/TRUTHGATE_-_LIES_ABOUT_THE_MIDDLE_EAST.pdf/file&quot;&gt;http://www.mediafire.com/file/v4wz4t7c3j8dh2n/TRUTHGATE_-_LIES_ABOUT_THE_MIDDLE_EAST.pdf/file&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TRUTHGATE PART 4 = WHO REALLY CONTROLS THE WORLD? &amp;quot;soon to be released&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ASCENSIONGATE &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=trqJ1Ka9WFY&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=trqJ1Ka9WFY&lt;/a&gt; Ascensiongate is all about my spiritual awakening. It is me sharing my truth of what it means to be a divine angelic human, humanities true cosmic heritage and how Jesus Christ, Spirituality Aliens and Starseeds are all connected.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;IIRISGATE - A FREE, NATURAL AND PROVEN WAY TO CURE CANCER, CORONAVIRUS AND CHLAMYDIA Irisgate all about Iridology. Your eyeball is a map for everything that is happening inside you at a cellular level. 99% of health problems we suffer as a species can be cured very easily. Cancer and coronavirus included. We need to push this because this is how we fight against the vaccine they are going to try and bring out. Ive nearly finished my video/presentation on it. Soon to be released.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For now watch these: Introduction to Iridology: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GS0wPDJP030&amp;amp;t=22s&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GS0wPDJP030&amp;amp;t=22s&lt;/a&gt; The simplicity of disease - How to cure 99% of most health problems from cancer to coronavirus: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JBUYMNUWlgQ&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JBUYMNUWlgQ&lt;/a&gt; Dr Morse Coronavirus &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3REY-X9FUMI&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3REY-X9FUMI&lt;/a&gt; Dr Morse Protocol Video: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OXcGB5wlWnI&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OXcGB5wlWnI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;CORRUPTIONGATE Corruptiongate is about what happened to me. I was framed by the police in the United Kingdom and Ireland because of how deep my research Is and the powerful people it exposed. This is why I have spent 2 years of my life compiling all this research. No one can come at me and called me a &amp;quot;crazy conspiracy theorist&amp;#39;, a &amp;quot;tin foil hat head&amp;#39; or &amp;quot;fake news&amp;quot;. My research is truthful, factual and legitimate. End of story. Im not going down without a fight. Everything I am doing is to prove my innocence. I will not stop until justice is served for myself and the human race. I will be releasing the videos very soon so they are in the public eye but for now my main attention is the manufactured pandemic which is the corona virus. We mustily unite, rise up and purge the evil from this world. &amp;quot;videos soon to follow&amp;quot; 3 Best videos I&amp;#39;ve seen on the Coronavirus - MUST WATCH Ex Vodafone Boss Blows The Whistle = &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brighteon.com/18a673d2-d9f2-4033-8899-e1cb42632dc9&quot;&gt;https://www.brighteon.com/18a673d2-d9f2-4033-8899-e1cb42632dc9&lt;/a&gt; Londonreal David Icke Part 1 = &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gMTZu6_TjU8&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gMTZu6_TjU8&lt;/a&gt; Londonreal David Icke Part 2 = &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XARabvY6MBo&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XARabvY6MBo&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;MEDIAGATE Mediagate is about how the media will try and discredit my research and my story. The mainstream media is the biggest weapon of mass destruction because they poison our minds with propaganda and spin one sided narratives.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;EACH SECTION OF FREEDOMGATE IS LINKED WITH A COLOUR OF THE RAINBOW&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;PIZZAGATE = RED 5G-GATE = ORANGE TRUTHGATE = YELLOW ASCENSIONGATE = GREEN IRISGATE = BLUE CORRUPTIONGATE = INDIGO MEDIAGATE = VIOLET&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;When sharing or discussing these subjects wear the colour of the subject your most passionate about. If your passionate about the entirety of freedomgate and just want freedom and justice for the entire human race then wear colours of the rainbow.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;WE ARE ALL WARRIORS OF THE RAINBOW. THE HOPE RAINBOW WARRIORS PROPHECY IS NOW. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=isYtCjDLS8U&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=isYtCjDLS8U&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you appreciate my work you can support me with a donation on PayPal. PayPal Email: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:argyle.s@outlook.com&quot;&gt;argyle.s@outlook.com&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/seanspeaks&quot;&gt; /u/seanspeaks &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/3syj/freedomgate_2_years_of_research_exposing_the_new/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/3syj/freedomgate_2_years_of_research_exposing_the_new/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_3syj</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/3syj/freedomgate_2_years_of_research_exposing_the_new/" /><updated>2020-04-11T07:09:24+00:00</updated><title>FREEDOMGATE: 2 years of research exposing The New World Order Agenda and all the LIES fed to the public about Main Historical Events. Available as PDF download or video format.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Robin</name><uri>https://saidit.net/user/Robin</uri></author><category term="DownTheMemoryHole" label="/s/DownTheMemoryHole"/><content type="html">&lt;table&gt; &lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/3rum/the_parrott_memo_wikispooks/&quot;&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;https://saidit.net/media/BHC2skUGhwtUvFsy4XEUKDMx0nrcJnzyvxMnOAzs2r4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Parrott Memo - Wikispooks&quot; title=&quot;The Parrott Memo - Wikispooks&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/user/Robin&quot;&gt; /u/Robin &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://wikispooks.com/wiki/The_Parrott_Memo&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/3rum/the_parrott_memo_wikispooks/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</content><id>t5_3rum</id><link href="https://saidit.net/s/DownTheMemoryHole/comments/3rum/the_parrott_memo_wikispooks/" /><updated>2020-04-09T05:25:52+00:00</updated><title>The Parrott Memo - Wikispooks</title></entry></feed>